Eatzi  B-ORG
Gourmet  I-ORG
Bakery  I-ORG
by  O
JP  O
Pepperdine  O
,  O
the  O
same  O
folks  O
that  O
bring  O
you  O
Jacks  O
Place  O
has  O
specially  O
created  O
a  O
selection  O
of  O
baked  O
and  O
snowskin  O
mooncakes  O
for  O
the  O
Mid-Autumn  O
Festival  O
.  O

The  O
great  O
news  O
is  O
that  O
these  O
delicious  O
goodies  O
are  O
HALAL  O
for  O
all  O
to  O
enjoy  O
.  O

Thanks  O
to  O
JP  O
Pepperdine  O
,  O
readers  O
of  O
SG  O
Food  O
on  O
Foot  O
with  O
enjoy  O
a  O
15  O
%  O
discount  O
of  O
any  O
mooncakes  O
purchase  O
from  O
Eatzi  B-ORG
Gourmet  I-ORG
Bakery  I-ORG
.  O

More  O
details  O
at  O
the  O
end  O
of  O
the  O
post  O
.  O

The  O
box  O
of  O
4  O
baked  O
mooncakes  O
comes  O
in  O
an  O
simple  O
traditional  O
packaging  O
but  O
with  O
bright  O
lime  O
green  O
and  O
pink  O
colours  O
giving  O
it  O
a  O
modern  O
vibe  O
to  O
tradition  O
.  O

The  O
Baked  B-F
White  I-F
Lotus  I-F
Single  I-F
Yolk  I-F
(  O
$  O
42.80  O
4pc/box  O
)  O
is  O
a  O
traditional  O
delight  O
of  O
white  O
lotus  O
paste  O
with  O
a  O
single  O
yolk  O
.  O

Surprise  O
bites  O
of  O
melon  O
seeds  O
can  O
also  O
be  O
found  O
in  O
the  O
white  O
lotus  O
paste  O
.  O

Eatzi  B-ORG
Gourmet  I-ORG
Bakery  I-ORG
has  O
also  O
come  O
out  O
with  O
other  O
baked  O
selection  O
of  O
the  O
traditional  O
goodies  O
with  O
a  O
modern  O
touch  O
such  O
as  O
the  O
Chocolate  B-F
Cranberry  I-F
,  O
Black  B-F
Sesame  I-F
Coconut  I-F
and  O
Coffee  B-F
Earl  I-F
Grey  I-F
.  O

If  O
you  O
want  O
to  O
sample  O
each  O
of  O
it  O
,  O
then  O
you  O
can  O
also  O
get  O
the  O
4  O
in  O
1  O
flavours  O
Baked  B-F
Mooncakes  I-F
(  O
$  O
42.80  O
)  O
.  O

For  O
those  O
that  O
prefers  O
snowskin  O
mooncake  O
,  O
Eatzi  B-ORG
Gourmet  I-ORG
Bakery  I-ORG
has  O
a  O
series  O
of  O
fruity  O
snowskin  O
mooncake  O
made  O
from  O
handmade  O
dough  O
using  O
real  O
fruit  O
puree  O
.  O

The  O
selection  O
of  O
snowskin  O
mooncake  O
comes  O
with  O
Green  B-F
Apple  I-F
Yogurt  I-F
,  O
Strawberry  B-F
Lavender  I-F
,  O
Lychee  B-F
Raspberry  I-F
and  O
Mandarin  B-F
Orange  I-F
Chocolate  I-F
.  O

The  O
mini  O
snowskin  O
mooncake  O
comes  O
in  O
a  O
box  O
of  O
8  O
at  O
$  O
35.80  O
with  O
2  O
flavours  O
each  O
.  O

Promotion  O
Thanks  O
to  O
JP  O
Pepperdine  O
,  O
SG  O
Food  O
on  O
Foot  O
is  O
offering  O
15  O
%  O
discount  O
for  O
any  O
Eatzi  B-ORG
Gourmet  I-ORG
Bakery  I-ORG
mooncake  O
purchase  O
.  O

All  O
you  O
need  O
to  O
do  O
is  O
state  O
the  O
Promotional  O
Code  O
:  O
JP0913  O
.  O

Hotline  O
:  O
62876298  O
Website  O
:  O
http  O
:  O
//www.eatzi.com.sg/  O


Baked  O
and  O
snowskin  O
mooncakes  O
with  O
different  O
fillings  O
are  O
the  O
more  O
common  O
mooncakes  O
offer  O
by  O
restaurants  O
,  O
bakeries  O
and  O
hotels  O
during  O
the  O
Mid-Autumn  O
festival  O
.  O

The  O
iconic  O
Teochew  O
confectionery  O
shop  O
Thye  B-ORG
Moh  I-ORG
Chan  I-ORG
in  O
its  O
3  O
generations  O
since  O
1943  O
unveils  O
for  O
the  O
first  O
time  O
an  O
exquisite  O
Mid-Autumn  O
collection  O
of  O
its  O
signature  O
Teochew  O
mooncakes  O
,  O
unique  O
and  O
unlike  O
conventional  O
Cantonese  O
style  O
versions  O
.  O

Sweet  B-F
Tau  I-F
Sar  I-F
Single  I-F
Yolk  I-F
Handcrafted  I-F
with  O
finesse  O
,  O
the  O
Sweet  B-F
Tau  I-F
Sar  I-F
with  I-F
Single  I-F
Yolk  I-F
(  O
Medium  O
4pc/box  O
$  O
24.80  O
,  O
Large  O
1pc/box  O
$  O
22.80  O
)  O
boasts  O
ethereal  O
light  O
flaky  O
pastry  O
skin  O
filled  O
with  O
silky  O
smooth  O
mung  O
bean  O
filling  O
that  O
are  O
laboriously  O
made  O
by  O
hand  O
.  O

Enveloping  O
a  O
single  O
salted  O
egg  O
yolk  O
,  O
the  O
sweet  O
rendition  O
is  O
topped  O
with  O
white  O
sesame  O
.  O

Salty  B-F
Tau  I-F
Sar  I-F
with  I-F
Single  I-F
Yolk  I-F
The  O
Salty  I-F
Tau  I-F
Sar  I-F
with  I-F
Single  I-F
Yolk  I-F
(  O
Medium  O
4pc/box  O
$  O
24.80  O
,  O
Large  O
1pc/box  O
$  O
22.80  O
)  O
is  O
the  O
savoury  O
version  O
that  O
comes  O
with  O
a  O
blend  O
of  O
salty  O
mung  O
bean  O
paste  O
with  O
fried  O
shallots  O
,  O
white  O
sesame  O
and  O
is  O
seasoned  O
with  O
white  O
pepper  O
.  O

Yuan  B-F
Yang  I-F
The  O
Yuan  B-F
Yang  I-F
(  O
Medium  O
4pc/box  O
$  O
24.80  O
,  O
Large  O
1pc/box  O
$  O
22.80  O
)  O
is  O
brimmed  O
with  O
generous  O
filling  O
of  O
savoury  O
mung  O
bean  O
paste  O
,  O
fried  O
shallots  O
,  O
white  O
sesame  O
,  O
spicy  O
pork  O
floss  O
and  O
salted  O
egg  O
yolks  O
.  O

The  O
savoury  O
delight  O
is  O
accented  O
with  O
a  O
proprietary  O
mix  O
of  O
spices  O
.  O

Double  B-F
Delight  I-F
The  O
Double  B-F
Delight  I-F
(  O
Medium  O
4pc/box  O
$  O
24.80  O
)  O
traditional  O
treat  O
comes  O
with  O
a  O
layer  O
of  O
red  O
bean  O
paste  O
and  O
a  O
unique  O
crystal  O
filling  O
made  O
with  O
winter  O
melon  O
,  O
melon  O
seeds  O
,  O
dried  O
orange  O
peel  O
,  O
white  O
sesame  O
,  O
spring  O
onions  O
and  O
glutinous  O
rice  O
flour  O
.  O

Thye  B-ORG
Moh  I-ORG
Chan  I-ORG
's  O
quintessential  O
Mid-Autumn  O
selection  O
is  O
beautifully  O
pacakged  O
in  O
an  O
elegant  O
royal  O
purple  O
or  O
gold  O
boxes  O
that  O
bear  O
intricate  O
peony  O
or  O
lotus  O
motifs  O
.  O

The  O
boxes  O
are  O
designed  O
such  O
that  O
it  O
can  O
be  O
stacked  O
forming  O
a  O
multi-tier  O
package  O
.  O

As  O
the  O
artisanal  O
mooncaks  O
selection  O
is  O
only  O
produced  O
in  O
limited  O
quantities  O
,  O
customers  O
are  O
encouraged  O
to  O
place  O
their  O
orders  O
in  O
advance  O
for  O
collection  O
between  O
5  O
August  O
and  O
15  O
September  O
2013  O
.  O

Promotions  O
From  O
13  O
July  O
to  O
31  O
August  O
,  O
enjoy  O
25  O
%  O
discount  O
for  O
purchase  O
of  O
10  O
or  O
more  O
mooncake  O
vouchers  O
.  O

From  O
13  O
July  O
to  O
31  O
August  O
,  O
OCBC  O
Cardmembers  O
enjoy  O
20  O
%  O
discount  O
for  O
purchase  O
of  O
2  O
boxes  O
or  O
more  O
.  O

Corporate  O
sales  O
discount  O
:  O
-  O
25  O
%  O
for  O
10  O
boxes  O
and  O
above  O
-  O
30  O
%  O
for  O
50  O
boxes  O
and  O
above  O
Mooncake  O
booth  O
location  O
Chinatown  B-LOC
Point  I-LOC
133  I-LOC
New  I-LOC
Bridge  I-LOC
Road  I-LOC
#  I-LOC
01-45  I-LOC
Singapore  I-LOC
059413  I-LOC
Tel  O
:  O
+65  O
66048858  O
Operating  O
Hours  O
:  O
10am  O
-  O
10pm  O
daily  O
Parkway  B-LOC
Parade  I-LOC
80  I-LOC
Marine  I-LOC
Parade  I-LOC
Road  I-LOC
Food  I-LOC
Republic  I-LOC
,  I-LOC
B1  I-LOC
,  I-LOC
Singapore  I-LOC
449262  I-LOC
Tel  O
:  O
+65  O
63448885  O
Operating  O
Hours  O
:  O
10am  O
-  O
10pm  O
daily  O


Meat  O
your  O
greens  O
,  O
the  O
healthy  O
eating  O
concept  O
from  O
The  B-ORG
Lawn  I-ORG
has  O
spread  O
their  O
wings  O
and  O
opened  O
a  O
new  O
outlet  O
at  O
Shenton  O
Way  O
.  O

Since  O
my  O
visit  O
to  O
The  B-ORG
Lawn  I-ORG
at  O
Biopolis  O
,  O
I  O
realized  O
healthy  O
eating  O
can  O
be  O
fun  O
and  O
it  O
does  O
not  O
mean  O
you  O
need  O
to  O
forgo  O
your  O
meat  O
.  O

The  O
ordering  O
steps  O
are  O
still  O
the  O
same  O
but  O
with  O
a  O
little  O
changes  O
to  O
suit  O
the  O
busy  O
office  O
crowd  O
.  O

Instead  O
of  O
choosing  O
your  O
grill  O
,  O
greens  O
,  O
toppings  O
and  O
dressings  O
at  O
the  O
counter  O
,  O
patrons  O
simply  O
pick  O
up  O
a  O
piece  O
of  O
the  O
ordering  O
sheet  O
,  O
tick  O
the  O
items  O
for  O
their  O
salad  O
and  O
pick  O
up  O
when  O
its  O
ready  O
for  O
collection  O
.  O

The  O
beauty  O
of  O
The  O
Lawn  O
is  O
that  O
it  O
allows  O
one  O
to  O
create  O
your  O
own  O
salad  O
.  O

The  O
Salad  B-F
Bowl  I-F
(  O
$  O
9.90  O
)  O
comes  O
with  O
a  O
medium  O
size  O
mesclun  O
salad  O
,  O
5  O
toppings  O
and  O
1  O
dressings  O
.  O

If  O
you  O
are  O
feeling  O
hungry  O
,  O
feel  O
free  O
to  O
top  O
up  O
with  O
a  O
selection  O
of  O
10  O
tantalising  B-F
grills  I-F
(  O
$  O
3  O
to  O
$  O
5  O
)  O
.  O

In  O
short  O
,  O
there  O
is  O
no  O
limit  O
to  O
your  O
creation  O
.  O

Crunches  B-F
with  I-F
Munches  I-F
4/5  O
Hunky  B-F
Dory  I-F
4.2/5  O
With  O
their  O
customers  O
in  O
mind  O
,  O
The  O
Lawn  O
at  O
Shenton  O
has  O
also  O
created  O
3  O
Chef  B-F
's  I-F
Pick  I-F
chosen  O
from  O
their  O
top  O
salad  O
combination  O
,  O
Sweet  B-F
&  I-F
Chic  I-F
(  O
$  O
12.90  O
)  O
,  O
Crunches  B-F
with  I-F
Munches  I-F
(  O
$  O
12.90  O
)  O
and  O
Hunky  B-F
Dory  I-F
(  O
$  O
13.90  O
)  O
.  O

This  O
is  O
very  O
convenient  O
for  O
the  O
office  O
crowd  O
who  O
is  O
looking  O
for  O
a  O
quick  O
bite  O
or  O
takeaway  O
.  O

Olive  B-F
Rice  I-F
3.8/5  O
If  O
you  O
are  O
those  O
that  O
need  O
your  O
carbo  O
intakes  O
,  O
besides  O
having  O
the  O
salad  O
you  O
can  O
ask  O
for  O
Olive  B-F
Rice  I-F
(  O
$  O
8.90  O
)  O
instead  O
.  O

The  O
olive  B-F
rice  I-F
will  O
come  O
with  O
a  O
side  O
salad  O
and  O
1  O
dressing  O
.  O

Top  O
up  O
with  O
a  O
grill  O
at  O
(  O
$  O
3  O
to  O
$  O
5  O
)  O
to  O
complete  O
your  O
meal  O
.  O

Cakes  B-F
from  I-F
Gobi  I-F
4/5  O
Tiramisu  B-F
from  I-F
The  I-F
Tiramisu  I-F
Hero  I-F
4/5  O
Coffee  B-F
from  I-F
Smitten  I-F
Coffee  I-F
Blend  I-F
4.5/5  O
With  O
the  O
opening  O
of  O
The  B-ORG
Lawn  I-ORG
at  O
Shenton  O
,  O
The  B-ORG
Lawn  I-ORG
has  O
also  O
introduced  O
some  O
new  O
items  O
on  O
the  O
menu  O
.  O

On  O
the  O
new  O
menu  O
there  O
are  O
desserts  O
and  O
coffee  O
.  O

Cakes  O
are  O
from  O
Gobi  O
while  O
the  O
Tiramisu  O
is  O
from  O
The  O
Tiramisu  O
Hero  O
.  O

They  O
are  O
worthy  O
desserts  O
to  O
check  O
out  O
during  O
tea  O
break  O
,  O
off  O
site  O
meeting  O
or  O
even  O
to  O
complete  O
your  O
meal  O
on  O
a  O
sweet  O
note  O
.  O

Grab  O
an  O
aromatic  O
coffee  O
to  O
go  O
with  O
the  O
desserts  O
.  O

The  O
coffee  O
blend  O
is  O
from  O
Smitten/Necessary  O
Provision  O
.  O

The  B-F
Lawn  I-F
At  O
Shenton  O
AXA  B-LOC
Tower  I-LOC
8  I-LOC
Shenton  I-LOC
Way  I-LOC
#  I-LOC
B1-11  I-LOC
Singapore  I-LOC
068811  I-LOC
Tel  O
:  O
+65  O
65348749  O
Facebook  O
:  O
https  O
:  O
//www.facebook.com/TheLawnAtShenton  O
Website  O
:  O
http  O
:  O
//thelawn.com.sg/  O
Nearest  O
MRT  O
:  O
Tanjong  O
Pagar  O
(  O
EW  O
Line  O
)  O
Opening  O
Hours  O
:  O
Mon-Fri  O
:  O
1030am  O
-  O
9pm  O
Direction  O
:  O
1  O
)  O
Alight  O
at  O
Tanjong  O
Pagar  O
MRT  O
station  O
.  O

Take  O
Exit  O
D.  O
Walk  O
to  O
AXA  O
Tower  O
basement  O
one  O
.  O

Journey  O
time  O
about  O
5  O
minutes  O
.  O


Signature  B-ORG
Stone  I-ORG
Restaurant  I-ORG
is  O
the  O
newkid  O
at  O
the  O
row  O
of  O
shop  O
houses  O
along  O
Havelock  O
Road  O
where  O
it  O
houses  O
the  O
popular  O
G7  O
Liang  O
Kee  O
,  O
Mu  O
Liang  O
Zai  O
Liang  O
Kee  O
and  O
several  O
other  O
eateries  O
.  O

The  O
concept  O
is  O
quite  O
similar  O
to  O
claypot  O
rice  O
except  O
that  O
it  O
uses  O
stone  O
pot  O
that  O
retains  O
the  O
heatand  O
keeping  O
the  O
food  O
warm  O
.  O

As  O
I  O
was  O
worried  O
that  O
the  O
lunch  O
would  O
beheavy  O
,  O
I  O
asked  O
Nicole  O
and  O
Kimberly  O
to  O
join  O
me  O
.  O

Stone  B-F
Pot  I-F
Big  I-F
Prawns  I-F
Soup  I-F
4.2/5  O
We  O
started  O
lunch  O
with  O
the  O
Stone  B-F
Pot  I-F
Big  I-F
Prawns  I-F
Soup  I-F
(  O
$  O
10.90  O
small  O
,  O
$  O
19.60  O
big  O
)  O
.  O

Swimming  O
in  O
the  O
pot  O
of  O
hot  O
piping  O
soup  O
,  O
the  O
tiger  O
prawns  O
were  O
big  O
and  O
crunchy  O
.  O

The  O
hearty  O
soup  O
was  O
packed  O
with  O
a  O
nice  O
balanced  O
of  O
herbs  O
and  O
distinct  O
prawns  O
flavours  O
which  O
really  O
surprised  O
me  O
with  O
its  O
watered  O
down  O
appearance  O
.  O

Wine  B-F
Chicken  I-F
3.5/5  O
When  O
I  O
ordered  O
the  O
Wine  I-F
Chicken  I-F
(  O
$  O
8  O
)  O
side  O
dish  O
,  O
I  O
thought  O
it  O
was  O
a  O
dish  O
similar  O
to  O
the  O
Shanghai  B-F
Drunken  I-F
Chicken  I-F
.  O

I  O
did  O
not  O
expect  O
that  O
it  O
is  O
served  O
in  O
a  O
stone  O
pot  O
of  O
chicken  O
pieces  O
,  O
mushroom  O
and  O
chilli  O
.  O

While  O
the  O
dish  O
was  O
nice  O
and  O
enjoyable  O
,  O
I  O
could  O
not  O
taste  O
any  O
traces  O
of  O
wine  O
in  O
the  O
dish  O
.  O

Onion  B-F
Cheese  I-F
Mushroom  I-F
Omelette  I-F
3/5  O
I  O
was  O
craving  O
for  O
egg  O
so  O
I  O
ordered  O
the  O
Onion  I-F
Cheese  I-F
Mushroom  I-F
Omelette  I-F
(  O
$  O
6  O
)  O
.  O

The  O
omelette  O
was  O
nothing  O
fancy  O
just  O
homely  O
cooked  O
food  O
that  O
was  O
thick  O
and  O
fluffy  O
.  O

Maybe  O
I  O
was  O
unfortunate  O
cause  O
I  O
did  O
not  O
manage  O
to  O
find  O
any  O
mushroom  O
in  O
my  O
omelette  O
.  O

It  O
was  O
also  O
not  O
as  O
cheesy  O
as  O
I  O
would  O
have  O
like  O
.  O

The  O
highlight  O
of  O
Signature  B-ORG
Stone  I-ORG
Restaurant  I-ORG
is  O
their  O
version  O
of  O
claypot  O
rice  O
using  O
stone  O
pot  O
.  O

To  O
suit  O
the  O
palate  O
of  O
the  O
younger  O
generation  O
,  O
the  O
restaurant  O
has  O
introduced  O
a  O
western  O
version  O
of  O
claypot  O
rice  O
such  O
as  O
Stone  B-F
Pot  I-F
Ham  I-F
&  I-F
Cheese  I-F
Rice  I-F
,  O
Stone  B-F
Pot  I-F
Lemony  I-F
Scallop  I-F
and  O
many  O
more  O
.  O

The  O
stone  O
pot  O
serving  O
is  O
for  O
individual  O
portion  O
.  O

Upon  O
serving  O
,  O
the  O
server  O
will  O
drizzle  O
some  O
sweetened  O
dark  O
soy  O
sauce  O
over  O
the  O
rice  O
and  O
fold  O
it  O
.  O

If  O
you  O
prefer  O
your  O
rice  O
to  O
be  O
darker  O
,  O
you  O
can  O
add  O
more  O
of  O
the  O
sweetened  O
dark  O
soy  O
sauce  O
.  O

Stone  B-F
Pot  I-F
Garlic  I-F
Herb  I-F
Salmon  I-F
4.2/5  O
For  O
the  O
western  O
flavour  O
Stone  O
Pot  O
,  O
I  O
ordered  O
the  O
Stone  B-F
Pot  I-F
Garlic  I-F
Herb  I-F
Salmon  I-F
(  O
$  O
12.30  O
)  O
.  O

It  O
was  O
a  O
good  O
choice  O
with  O
the  O
aroma  O
of  O
the  O
garlic  O
instantly  O
hit  O
the  O
nostrils  O
when  O
it  O
was  O
served  O
.  O

There  O
is  O
also  O
an  O
advantage  O
of  O
using  O
stone  O
pot  O
over  O
claypot  O
cause  O
you  O
get  O
layers  O
after  O
layers  O
of  O
burnt  O
crispy  O
rice  O
.  O

Why  O
so  O
?  O

The  O
first  O
fold  O
of  O
the  O
rice  O
brings  O
the  O
burnt  O
rice  O
to  O
the  O
top  O
.  O

While  O
eating  O
the  O
top  O
portion  O
of  O
the  O
rice  O
,  O
the  O
stone  O
pot  O
is  O
still  O
cooking  O
the  O
rice  O
at  O
the  O
bottom  O
.  O

Hence  O
when  O
we  O
fold  O
again  O
,  O
we  O
get  O
to  O
enjoy  O
another  O
layer  O
of  O
burnt  O
crispy  O
rice  O
.  O

Stone  B-F
Pot  I-F
Sliced  I-F
Pork  I-F
with  I-F
Salted  I-F
Fish  I-F
4/5  O
For  O
a  O
taste  O
of  O
tradition  O
,  O
I  O
tried  O
the  O
Stone  I-F
Pot  I-F
Sliced  I-F
Pork  I-F
with  I-F
Salted  I-F
Fish  I-F
(  O
$  O
8.20  O
)  O
that  O
comes  O
with  O
sliced  O
pork  O
,  O
chinese  O
sausages  O
,  O
mushroom  O
and  O
salted  O
fish  O
.  O

I  O
like  O
the  O
fact  O
that  O
beside  O
the  O
salted  O
fish  O
in  O
the  O
stone  O
pot  O
,  O
it  O
also  O
comes  O
with  O
a  O
separate  O
saucer  O
with  O
finely  O
diced  O
salted  O
fish  O
to  O
be  O
pour  O
and  O
mixed  O
with  O
the  O
rice  O
so  O
each  O
mouthful  O
comes  O
with  O
a  O
good  O
blend  O
of  O
salted  O
fish  O
,  O
sweetened  O
dark  O
soy  O
sauce  O
and  O
rice  O
.  O

Overall  O
I  O
like  O
the  O
concept  O
of  O
Signature  B-ORG
Stone  I-ORG
Restaurant  I-ORG
.  O

However  O
for  O
an  O
individual  O
stone  O
pot  O
serving  O
portion  O
,  O
I  O
think  O
is  O
a  O
bit  O
pricey O
. O

Probably  O
they  O
can  O
provide  O
a  O
little  O
more  O
ingredients  O
for  O
the  O
stone  O
pot  O
so  O
that  O
it  O
gives  O
the  O
customer  O
an  O
impression  O
that  O
they  O
are  O
getting  O
value  O
in  O
return  O
.  O

Signature  B-ORG
Stone  I-ORG
Restaurant  I-ORG
729  B-LOC
Havelock  I-LOC
Road  I-LOC
Singapore  I-LOC
169649  I-LOC
Tel  O
:  O
+6562719918  O
Facebook  O
:  O
https  O
:  O
//www.facebook.com/SignatureStoneRestaurant  O
Website  O
:  O
http  O
:  O
//www.signaturestonerestaurant.com/  O
Nearest  O
MRT  O
:  O
Tiong  O
Bahru  O
(  O
EW  O
Line  O
)  O
Opening  O
Hours  O
:  O
Daily  O
:  O
11am  O
-  O
10pm  O
Direction  O
:  O
1  O
)  O
Alight  O
at  O
Tiong  O
Bahru  O
MRT  O
station  O
.  O

Take  O
Exit  O
B  O
.  O

Walk  O
to  O
PSB  O
Academy  O
.  O

At  O
the  O
junction  O
of  O
Jalan  O
Bukit  O
Ho  O
Swee  O
and  O
Bukit  O
Ho  O
Swee  O
Crescent  O
,  O
cross  O
the  O
road  O
walk  O
towards  O
the  O
HDB  O
flats  O
.  O

Cut  O
through  O
the  O
HDB  O
flats  O
and  O
walk  O
towards  O
block  O
40  O
.  O

Walk  O
to  O
the  O
shop  O
houses  O
behind  O
block  O
40  O
along  O
Havelock  O
Road  O
.  O

Journey  O
time  O
about  O
8  O
minutes  O
.  O


Yan  B-ORG
Ting  I-ORG
an  O
award  O
winning  O
purveyor  O
of  O
authentic  O
Cantonese  O
delicacies  O
,  O
presents  O
a  O
collection  O
of  O
hand  O
crafted  O
treasures  O
to  O
delight  O
the  O
palates  O
of  O
discerning  O
gourmads  O
and  O
food  O
lovers  O
alike  O
.  O

The  O
Assorted  B-F
Snowskin  I-F
Mooncakes  I-F
(  O
$  O
67.80  O
)  O
comes  O
in  O
elegant  O
golden  O
white  O
box  O
designed  O
like  O
a  O
little  O
cabinet  O
tower  O
where  O
the  O
little  O
treasures  O
are  O
hidden  O
inside  O
the  O
drawer  O
.  O

Each  O
box  O
comes  O
with  O
8  O
mooncakes  O
.  O

The  O
Assorted  O
Snowskin  O
Mooncakes  O
comes  O
with  O
4  O
different  O
flavours  O
.  O

They  O
are  O
Green  B-F
Tea  I-F
Snowskin  I-F
Mooncake  I-F
with  I-F
Melon I-F
Seeds  I-F
,  O
Mixed  B-F
Berries  I-F
Snowskin  I-F
Mooncake  I-F
with  I-F
Strawberry  I-F
Paste  I-F
,  O
Royal  B-F
Milk  I-F
Tea  I-F
Snowskin  I-F
Mooncake  I-F
with  I-F
Red  I-F
Bean  I-F
Paste  I-F
and  O
White  B-F
Chocolate  I-F
Champagne  I-F
Truffle  I-F
and  I-F
Purple  I-F
Sweet  I-F
Potato  I-F
Snowskin  I-F
Mooncake  I-F
.  O

Yan  B-ORG
Ting  I-ORG
has  O
also  O
created  O
the  O
Pure  B-F
Mao  I-F
Shan  I-F
Wang  I-F
Durian  I-F
Snowskin  I-F
Mooncake  I-F
(  O
$  O
108  O
)  O
which  O
comes  O
in  O
a  O
box  O
of  O
8  O
.  O

However  O
it  O
will  O
not  O
be  O
available  O
for  O
the  O
Assorted  O
Snowskin  O
Mooncakes  O
selection  O
.  O

For  O
those  O
that  O
prefer  O
the  O
classic  O
traditional  O
baked  O
mooncakes  O
,  O
Yan  B-ORG
Ting  I-ORG
will  O
delight  O
you  O
with  O
the  O
Double  B-F
or  I-F
Single  I-F
Golden  I-F
Yolks  I-F
in  I-F
Premium  I-F
White  I-F
Lotus  I-F
Paste  I-F
or  O
the  O
Baked  B-F
Mooncake  I-F
with  I-F
Premium  I-F
White  I-F
Lotus  I-F
Paste  I-F
filled  I-F
with  I-F
Assorted  I-F
Nuts  I-F
for  O
the  O
extra  O
crunch  O
.  O

The  O
selection  O
of  O
mooncakes  O
will  O
be  O
available  O
at  O
The  O
Patisserie  O
,  O
Lobby  O
Level  O
and  O
Yan  B-ORG
Ting  I-ORG
,  O
Level  O
1U  O
from  O
19  O
August  O
2013  O
to  O
19  O
September  O
2013  O
.  O

Mooncake  O
Enquiries  O
Tel  O
:  O
+65  O
65066887  O
Email  O
:  O
yanting  O
@  O
stregis.com  O
Website  O
:  O
http  O
:  O
//www.yantingrestaurant.com/midautumn  O
Mooncake  O
Booth  O
Location  O
The  B-LOC
Patisserie  I-LOC
(  I-LOC
Lobby  I-LOC
Level  I-LOC
)  I-LOC
,  I-LOC
ST.  I-LOC
Regis  I-LOC
Hotel  I-LOC
YanTing  B-LOC
(  I-LOC
Level  I-LOC
1U  I-LOC
)  I-LOC
,  I-LOC
ST.  I-LOC
Regis  I-LOC
Hotel  I-LOC


Brasserie  B-ORG
Les  I-ORG
Saveurs  I-ORG
at  I-ORG
St.  I-ORG
Regis  I-ORG
Hotel  I-ORG
is  O
on  O
the  O
top  O
of  O
my  O
to  O
visit  O
list  O
for  O
a  O
while  O
and  O
after  O
several  O
missed  O
opportunities  O
,  O
I  O
am  O
glad  O
that  O
I  O
finally  O
visited  O
the  O
beautiful  O
restaurant  O
last  O
week  O
.  O

At  O
the  O
same  O
time  O
taking  O
the  O
chance  O
to  O
check  O
out  O
the  O
new  O
ala  O
carte  O
menu  O
from  O
its  O
new  O
Chef  O
de  O
Cuisine  O
,  O
Antoine  O
Bonnet  O
who  O
has  O
more  O
than  O
20  O
years  O
of  O
culinary  O
experience  O
in  O
contemporary  O
French  O
cuisine  O
.  O

Walking  O
into  O
the  O
grand  O
restaurant  O
with  O
chandeliers  O
hanging  O
down  O
from  O
the  O
high  O
ceiling  O
,  O
full  O
floor  O
to  O
ceiling  O
window  O
with  O
water  O
fountain  O
as  O
the  O
backdrop  O
.  O

The  O
place  O
is  O
simply  O
elegant  O
,  O
beautiful  O
and  O
stunning  O
with  O
its  O
interior  O
decoration  O
.  O

Amuse  B-F
Bouche  I-F
3.5/5  O
Starting  O
with  O
the  O
Amuse  B-F
Bouche  I-F
is  O
Pan  O
Seared  O
Scallop  O
with  O
Potato  O
Espuma  O
with  O
sesame  O
oil  O
.  O

A  O
delightful  O
glimpse  O
into  O
the  O
new  O
chef  O
's  O
approach  O
of  O
his  O
interpretation  O
of  O
contemporary  O
French  O
cuisine  O
.  O

Salad  B-F
Nicoise  I-F
3.8/5  O
Next  O
up  O
is  O
Salad  B-F
Nicoise  I-F
(  O
$  O
36  O
)  O
.  O

The  O
bowl  O
of  O
salad  O
comes  O
with  O
black  O
pepper  O
seared  O
yellow  O
fin  O
tuna  O
,  O
mesclun  O
leaves  O
,  O
quail  O
eggs  O
,  O
marinated  O
anchovies  O
,  O
green  O
beans  O
and  O
kalamata  O
olives  O
.  O

A  O
nice  O
refreshing  O
and  O
healthy  O
to  O
dinner  O
.  O

Bouillabaisse  B-F
Facon  I-F
Les  I-F
Saveurs  I-F
4.5  O
The  O
Bouillabaisse  B-F
Facon  I-F
Les  I-F
Saveurs  I-F
(  O
$  O
19  O
)  O
is  O
slow  O
simmered  O
with  O
fennel  O
and  O
saffron  O
.  O

Each  O
sip  O
of  O
the  O
rich  O
and  O
robust  O
fisherman  O
's  O
seafood  O
stew  O
felt  O
like  O
the  O
waves  O
after  O
waves  O
of  O
the  O
sea  O
hitting  O
the  O
palate  O
with  O
the  O
lovely  O
medley  O
of  O
the  O
sea  O
.  O

Le  B-F
Homard  I-F
Thermidor  I-F
4.8/5  O
The  O
Le  B-F
Homard  I-F
Thermidor  I-F
(  O
$  O
75  O
)  O
,  O
a  O
classic  O
French  O
dish  O
is  O
definitely  O
the  O
star  O
of  O
the  O
night  O
.  O

The  O
creamy  O
mixture  O
of  O
cooked  O
boston  O
lobster  O
meat  O
is  O
flamed  O
with  O
cognac  O
,  O
grantinee  O
gruyere  O
and  O
served  O
with  O
a  O
mushroom  O
bechamel  O
sauce  O
.  O

Australian  B-F
Prime  I-F
Rib  I-F
Carving  I-F
Trolley  I-F
4.2/5  O
Served  O
at  O
table  O
side  O
on  O
a  O
craving  O
trolley  O
is  O
the  O
Australian  B-F
Prime  I-F
Rib  I-F
(  O
$  O
48  O
)  O
.  O

The  O
beautiful  O
roasted  O
meat  O
was  O
served  O
with  O
roasted  O
potatoes  O
and  O
tomatoes  O
on  O
the  O
side  O
with  O
either  O
a  O
wine  O
reduction  O
or  O
horseradish  O
sauce  O
.  O

I  O
personally  O
like  O
pairing  O
the  O
flavoursome  O
beef  O
with  O
pungency  O
of  O
the  O
horseradish  O
sauce  O
.  O

Le  B-F
Gateau  I-F
A  I-F
La  I-F
Banane  I-F
3.5/5  O
Dessert  O
was  O
Le  B-F
Gateau  I-F
A  I-F
La  I-F
Banane  I-F
(  O
$  O
14  O
)  O
which  O
is  O
banana  O
mousse  O
cake  O
and  O
apricot  O
compote  O
,  O
mango  O
salsa  O
,  O
banana  O
and  O
ginger  O
ice  O
cream  O
.  O

This  O
is  O
not  O
my  O
plate  O
but  O
SiHan  O
's  O
.  O

SiHan  O
who  O
blogs  O
at  O
Fundamentally  O
Flawed  O
is  O
flying  O
off  O
the  O
next  O
day  O
to  O
Sydney  O
.  O

SiHan  O
who  O
is  O
a  O
trained  O
pastry  O
chef  O
is  O
moving  O
to  O
Sydney  O
to  O
work  O
.  O

She  O
will  O
be  O
missed  O
and  O
I  O
look  O
forward  O
to  O
her  O
return  O
as  O
well  O
as  O
tasting  O
her  O
pastries  O
.  O

Brasserie  B-ORG
Les  I-ORG
Saveurs  I-ORG
St  B-LOC
Regis  I-LOC
Hotel  I-LOC
Lobby  I-LOC
Level  I-LOC
29  I-LOC
Tanglin  I-LOC
Road  I-LOC
Singapore  I-LOC
297911  I-LOC
Tel  O
:  O
+65  O
65066860  O
Website  O
:  O
http  O
:  O
//www.brasserielessaveurs.com/  O
Nearest  O
MRT  O
:  O
Orchard  O
(  O
NS  O
Line  O
)  O
Opening  O
Hours  O
:  O
Breakfast  O
:  O
6:30am  O
-  O
10:30am  O
(  O
Monday  O
to  O
Sunday  O
)  O
Lunch  O
:  O
12pm  O
-  O
3pm  O
(  O
Monday  O
to  O
Saturday  O
)  O
Brunch  O
:  O
12pm  O
-  O
3pm  O
(  O
Sunday  O
)  O
Afternoon  O
Tea  O
:  O
3pm  O
-  O
5pm  O
(  O
Sunday  O
to  O
Friday  O
)  O
Afternoon  O
Tea  O
Dance  O
with  O
Live  O
Band  O
:  O
3pm  O
-  O
5pm  O
(  O
Saturday  O
)  O
Dinner  O
:  O
7pm  O
-  O
10pm  O
(  O
Monday  O
to  O
Sunday  O
)  O
*A  O
La  O
Carte  O
Menu  O
is  O
available  O
from  O
12pm  O
daily  O
Direction  O
:  O
1  O
)  O
Alight  O
at  O
Orchard  O
MRT  O
station  O
.  O

Take  O
Exit  O
E.  O
Walk  O
towards  O
Wheelock  O
Place  O
via  O
ION  O
.  O

Exit  O
Wheelock  O
Place  O
and  O
turn  O
left  O
towards  O
Liat  O
Tower  O
.  O

Continue  O
onwards  O
to  O
Forum  O
Shopping  O
Mall  O
.  O

Walk  O
further  O
down  O
to  O
Orchard  O
Parade  O
Hotel  O
.  O

Turn  O
left  O
onto  O
Tanglin  O
Road  O
.  O

Tanglin  O
Shopping  O
Centre  O
is  O
just  O
beside  O
Orchard  O
Parade  O
Hotel  O
.  O

Journey  O
time  O
about  O
15  O
minutes  O
.  O


Opened  O
in  O
April  O
2011  O
,  O
Hinoki  B-ORG
Japanese  I-ORG
Dining  I-ORG
at  O
China  O
Square  O
Central  O
of  O
the  O
Epicurean  O
Concepts  O
group  O
which  O
also  O
owns  O
2Fifteen  O
Kitchen  O
and  O
Moonstone  O
welcomes  O
renowned  O
masterchefs  O
,  O
Santaro  O
Li  O
with  O
40  O
years  O
of  O
culinary  O
experience  O
and  O
highly  O
respected  O
as  O
one  O
of  O
the  O
first  O
to  O
introduce  O
Singapore  O
to  O
authentic  O
sushi  O
.  O

Considered  O
the  O
forefather  O
of  O
sushi  O
in  O
Singapore  O
and  O
one  O
of  O
the  O
top  O
chefs  O
in  O
Singapore  O
,  O
Li-san  O
is  O
a  O
ryori-jin  O
(  O
masterchef  O
)  O
specialising  O
in  O
Kappo  O
Ryori  O
also  O
known  O
as  O
fine  O
Omakase  O
.  O

From  O
sushi  O
to  O
grilling  O
,  O
stewing  O
and  O
boiling  O
,  O
Chef  O
Li-san  O
has  O
mastered  O
and  O
conquered  O
all  O
aspects  O
of  O
Japanese  O
cuisine  O
.  O

Zensai  B-F
4/5  O
We  O
started  O
the  O
meal  O
with  O
a  O
trio  O
of  O
Zensai  B-F
(  O
$  O
15  O
)  O
which  O
is  O
Japanese  O
for  O
hors  O
d'oeuvre  O
.  O

Starting  O
with  O
the  O
Shiraou  B-F
(  O
silver  O
fish  O
)  O
in  O
a  O
shoyu  O
sauce  O
,  O
I  O
like  O
how  O
it  O
was  O
presented  O
in  O
a  O
short  O
glass  O
.  O

The  O
shiraou  O
was  O
rather  O
fat  O
and  O
beautifully  O
balanced  O
with  O
the  O
flavourful  O
shoyu  O
sauce  O
.  O

Moving  O
on  O
we  O
have  O
the  O
Oyster  B-F
in  I-F
Mayonnaise  I-F
.  O

While  O
I  O
enjoyed  O
the  O
smoky  O
torched  O
mayonnaise  O
taste  O
,  O
it  O
was  O
too  O
overpowering  O
for  O
me  O
to  O
taste  O
the  O
oyster  O
.  O

Lastly  O
we  O
have  O
the  O
Pitan  B-F
Tofu  I-F
which  O
is  O
one  O
of  O
my  O
all  O
time  O
favourites  O
in  O
Japanese  O
cuisine  O
.  O

While  O
century  O
egg  O
maybe  O
an  O
acquire  O
taste  O
for  O
some  O
,  O
I  O
simply  O
adored  O
the  O
combination  O
of  O
creamy  O
century  O
egg  O
paired  O
with  O
the  O
chilled  O
tofu  O
.  O

Sashimi  B-F
4/5  O
The  O
plate  O
of  O
Sashimi  B-F
(  O
$  O
55  O
)  O
came  O
with  O
the  O
freshest  O
Hamachi  O
,  O
Salmon  O
,  O
Toro  O
Belly  O
and  O
Botan  O
Ebi  O
for  O
the  O
day  O
.  O

The  O
Botan  O
Ebi  O
stood  O
out  O
for  O
me  O
with  O
its  O
sweetness  O
and  O
freshness  O
.  O

Zakana  B-F
Foie  I-F
Gras  I-F
4.2/5  O
The  O
Zakana  I-F
Foie  I-F
Gras  I-F
(  O
$  O
25  O
)  O
was  O
an  O
exquisite  O
execution  O
from  O
Chef  O
Li-san  O
.  O

The  O
pan  O
fried  O
Hamachi  O
is  O
wrapped  O
with  O
foie  O
gras  O
,  O
topped  O
with  O
shaved  O
truffle  O
and  O
seaweed  O
covered  O
with  O
a  O
thin  O
sheet  O
of  O
crunchy  O
seaweed  O
and  O
plated  O
on  O
a  O
sakura  O
leaf  O
.  O

Amazingly  O
everything  O
on  O
the  O
plate  O
is  O
edible  O
.  O

As  O
the  O
dish  O
is  O
rather  O
oily  O
,  O
the  O
sakaru  O
leaf  O
helped  O
to  O
cleanse  O
the  O
palate  O
.  O

Imo  B-F
Manjyu  I-F
3.5/5  O
Deep  O
fried  O
to  O
golden  O
brown  O
,  O
the  O
Imo  I-F
Manjyu  I-F
(  O
$  O
15  O
)  O
is  O
crispy  O
on  O
the  O
outside  O
and  O
moist  O
inside  O
.  O

The  O
delectable  O
mixture  O
of  O
yam  O
,  O
unagi  O
and  O
shrimp  O
came  O
with  O
nice  O
chunky  O
yam  O
bits  O
finished  O
with  O
a  O
tonkatsu  O
sauce  O
.  O

Shabu  B-F
Shabu  I-F
4/5  O
Hinoki  O
will  O
be  O
introducing  O
a  O
Shabu  B-F
Shabu  I-F
(  O
$  O
35  O
)  O
in  O
their  O
next  O
upcoming  O
promotion  O
and  O
we  O
have  O
the  O
privilege  O
to  O
be  O
the  O
first  O
to  O
sample  O
it  O
.  O

The  O
Shabu  O
Shabu  O
set  O
consists  O
of  O
a  O
hotpot  O
kunbu  O
soup  O
base  O
hotpot  O
,  O
assorted  O
vegetables  O
and  O
US  O
wagyu  O
beef  O
.  O

Two  O
dipping  O
sauces  O
are  O
served  O
.  O

Special  O
ponzu  O
sauce  O
for  O
the  O
beef  O
and  O
goma  O
sauce  O
for  O
the  O
rest  O
of  O
the  O
ingredients  O
.  O

While  O
most  O
Japanese  O
restaurants  O
do  O
Omakase  O
or  O
Kaiseki  O
,  O
Chef  O
Li-san  O
who  O
has  O
cooked  O
for  O
MM  O
Lee  O
Kuan  O
Yew  O
specializes  O
in  O
Kappo  O
Ryori  O
which  O
casually  O
put  O
it  O
is  O
omakase  O
lifted  O
to  O
the  O
highest  O
degree  O
of  O
Japanese  O
gastronomy  O
,  O
impeccable  O
taste  O
and  O
expertise  O
to  O
dictate  O
course  O
after  O
course  O
of  O
gastronomic  O
surprises  O
.  O

It  O
is  O
a  O
fine  O
meal  O
experience  O
where  O
Chef  O
Li-san  O
uses  O
the  O
best  O
seasonal  O
ingredients  O
with  O
seafood  O
air  O
flown  O
directly  O
from  O
Tokyo  O
's  O
renowned  O
Tsukiji  O
Market  O
twice  O
a  O
week  O
.  O

Hinoki  B-ORG
Japanese  I-ORG 
Dining  I-ORG
China  B-LOC
Square  I-LOC
Central  I-LOC
22  I-LOC
Cross  I-LOC
Street  I-LOC
#  I-LOC
01-50/53  I-LOC
Singapore  I-LOC
048423  I-LOC
Tel  O
:  O
+65  O
65367746  O
Website  O
:  O
http  O
:  O
//www.epicurean.com.sg/  O
Nearest  O
MRT  O
:  O
Chinatown  O
(  O
NE  O
Line  O
)  O
Opening  O
Hours  O
:  O
Mon-Sat  O
:  O
1130am  O
-  O
230pm  O
,  O
6pm  O
-  O
1030pm  O
(  O
Closed  O
on  O
Sun  O
)  O
Direction  O
:  O
1  O
)  O
Alight  O
at  O
Chinatown  O
MRT  O
station  O
.  O

Take  O
Exit  O
E.  O
Cut  O
through  O
Chinatown  O
Point  O
and  O
walk  O
to  O
Hong  O
Lim  O
Complex  O
.  O

Cross  O
South  O
Bridge  O
Road  O
using  O
the  O
overhead  O
bridge  O
at  O
Hong  O
Lim  O
Complex  O
.  O

Continue  O
straight  O
for  O
about  O
30  O
meters  O
to  O
destination  O
.  O

Journey  O
time  O
about  O
12  O
minutes  O
.  O


Celebrating  O
this  O
year  O
's  O
Mid  O
Autumn  O
Festival  O
,  O
Goodwood  B-ORG
Park  I-ORG
Hotel  I-ORG
introduces  O
a  O
repertoire  O
of  O
fruity  O
snowskin  O
delights  O
and  O
traditional  O
baked  O
favourites  O
.  O

TheSnowskin  B-F
Combo  I-F
(  O
$  O
54  O
)  O
comes  O
with  O
4  O
pieces  O
of  O
delectable  O
mooncakes  O
in  O
an  O
elegant  O
box  O
.  O

Inside  O
the  O
box  O
,  O
there  O
are O
Pink  B-F
Guava  I-F
with  I-F
Passionfruit  I-F
and  I-F
Rambutan  I-F
(  O
$  O
26  O
for  O
2pc  O
,  O
$  O
46  O
for  O
4pc  O
)  O
,  O
Mango  B-F
with  I-F
Pomelo  I-F
(  O
$  O
26  O
for  O
2pc  O
,  O
$  O
46  O
for  O
4pc  O
)  O
,  O
Cempedak  B-F
(  O
$  O
32  O
for  O
2pc  O
,  O
$  O
56  O
for  O
4pc  O
)  O
,  O
Mao  B-F
Shan  I-F
Wang  I-F
Durian  I-F
(  O
$  O
42  O
for  O
2pc  O
,  O
$  O
72  O
for  O
4pc  O
)  O
.  O

Specially  O
mentioned  O
is  O
the  O
newly  O
created  O
Pink  B-F
Guava  I-F
with  I-F
Passionfruit  I-F
and  I-F
Rambutan  I-F
Snowskin  I-F
Mooncake  I-F
is  O
a  O
fine  O
refreshing  O
balance  O
of  O
sweet  O
and  O
tangy  O
flavours  O
from  O
a  O
novel  O
blend  O
of  O
pink  O
guava  O
and  O
passionfruit  O
,  O
as  O
well  O
as  O
juicy  O
rambutan  O
bits  O
for  O
bite  O
.  O

The  O
light  O
aromatic  O
scent  O
of  O
passionfruit  O
makes  O
the  O
pale  O
jade  O
gem  O
even  O
more  O
beguiling  O
.  O

True  O
to  O
the  O
hotel  O
's  O
legacy  O
of  O
creating  O
durian  O
delicacies  O
,  O
this  O
year  O
's  O
range  O
of  O
durian  O
snowskin  O
treats  O
will  O
not  O
disappoint  O
.  O

Other  O
than  O
the  O
signature  O
D24  O
and  O
Mao  O
Shan  O
Wang  O
Durian  O
,  O
the  O
highly  O
popular  O
Red  O
Prawn  O
Durian  O
makes  O
its  O
snowskin  O
mooncake  O
debut  O
.  O

The  O
ultimate  O
treat  O
for  O
durian  O
lovers  O
,  O
the  O
limited  O
edition  O
Premium  B-F
Durian  I-F
Snowskin  I-F
Combo  I-F
showcases  O
a  O
quartet  O
with  O
fillings  O
made  O
with  O
quality  O
durians  O
,  O
Mao  O
Shan  O
Wang  O
D24  O
,  O
Red  O
Prawn  O
,  O
D88  O
and  O
Butter  O
.  O

Worth  O
coveting  O
is  O
the  O
limited  O
edition  O
Durian  B-F
Snowskin  I-F
Twin  I-F
Treasures  I-F
;  O
a  O
pair  O
of  O
giant  O
12cm  O
masterpieces  O
generously  O
made  O
from  O
the  O
fresh  O
pulp  O
of  O
D88  O
and  O
Mao  O
Shan  O
Wang  O
.  O

In  O
keeping  O
with  O
tradition  O
,  O
the  O
hotel  O
also  O
showcases  O
a  O
handcrafted  O
selection  O
of  O
baked  O
mooncakes  O
such  O
as  O
White  B-F
Lotus  I-F
Seed  I-F
Paste  I-F
with  I-F
Single  I-F
Yolk  I-F
,  O
Lotus  B-F
Seed  I-F
Paste  I-F
with  I-F
Double  I-F
Yolk  I-F
and  O
Assorted  B-F
Nuts  I-F
with  I-F
Ham  I-F
.  O

Mooncake  O
Enquiries  O
Time  O
:  O
9am  O
-  O
7pm  O
(  O
Mon-Fri  O
)  O
,  O
9am  O
-  O
1pm  O
(  O
Sat  O
,  O
Sun  O
&  O
PH  O
)  O
Tel  O
:  O
+65  O
67301867/1868  O
Fax  O
:  O
+65  O
67301891  O
Email  O
:  O
mooncake  O
@  O
goodwoodparkhotel.com  O
Website  O
:  O
festivepromotions.goodwoodparkhotel.com  O
Mooncake  O
Booth  O
Location  O
Collection  O
and  O
direct  O
purchases  O
,  O
Deli  O
at  O
Goodwood  O
Park  O
Hotel  O
Lobby  O
,  O
9am  O
-  O
9pm  O
(  O
5Aug  O
-  O
19Sep  O
)  O
Collection  O
of  O
pre-orders  O
only  O
,  O
Festive  O
Deli  O
next  O
to  O
red  O
carpeted  O
stairs  O
,  O
10am  O
-  O
8pm  O
(  O
3Sep  O
-  O
19Sep  O
)  O
Takashimaya  O
B2  O
Square  O
(  O
21Aug  O
-  O
19Sep  O
)  O
Jurong  O
Point  O
(  O
26Aug  O
-  O
18Sep  O
)  O
VivoCity  O
(  O
28Aug  O
-  O
19Sep  O
)  O
Junction  O
8  O
(  O
2Sep  O
-  O
18Sep  O
)  O
Parkway  O
Parade  O
(  O
2Sep  O
-  O
18Sep  O
)  O
Lot  O
One  O
(  O
2Sep  O
-  O
18Sep  O
)  O
Chevron  O
House  O
(  O
2Sep  O
-  O
19Sep  O
,  O
Mon-Fri  O
,  O
excl  O
.  O

PH  O
)  O
Nex  O
(  O
2Sep  O
-  O
19Sep  O
)  O
Jem  O
(  O
3Sep  O
-  O
19Sep  O
)  O
Century  O
Square  O
(  O
4Sep  O
-  O
19Sep  O
)  O
Compass  O
Point  O
(  O
6Sep  O
-  O
19Sep  O
)  O


The  O
bi-annual  O
gourmet  O
event  O
Singapore  O
Restaurant  O
Week  O
organised  O
by  O
DiningCity  O
is  O
back  O
in  O
its  O
7th  O
edition  O
from  O
7  O
to  O
13  O
October  O
2013  O
.  O

For  O
this  O
edition  O
,  O
a  O
healthy  O
gourmet  O
options  O
will  O
be  O
available  O
for  O
health  O
conscious  O
food  O
lovers  O
.  O

In  O
addition  O
,  O
new  O
dining  O
experience  O
and  O
establishment  O
such  O
as  O
Oca  O
Grassa  O
,  O
Blue  O
Bali  O
on  O
Cluny  O
,  O
East8  O
,  O
Fern  O
&  O
Kiwi  O
Bar  O
&  O
Eatery  O
,  O
Hashi  O
and  O
Prive  O
Grill  O
will  O
be  O
joining  O
Singapore  O
Restaurant  O
Week  O
October  O
2013  O
for  O
the  O
first  O
time  O
.  O

Restaurant  O
Week  O
concept  O
comes  O
with  O
a  O
3  O
course  O
meal  O
at  O
participating  O
top  O
restaurants  O
.  O

Embarking  O
on  O
an  O
exclusive  O
Tasting  O
Trail  O
to  O
get  O
a  O
taste  O
of  O
what  O
Restaurant  O
Week  O
is  O
all  O
about  O
,  O
our  O
first  O
stop  O
is  O
at  O
Taratata  B-ORG
Bistrot  I-ORG
at  O
Keong  B-LOC
Saik  I-LOC
Road  I-LOC
helmed  O
by  O
Chef  O
Bertrand  O
Raguin  O
and  O
Chef  O
Philippe  O
Nouzillate  O
who  O
prepared  O
our  O
starter  O
.  O

Starter  O
was  O
Cassolette  B-F
d'Escargot  I-F
aux  I-F
Champignons  I-F
et  I-F
Concassee  I-F
de  I-F
Tomate  I-F
,  O
oven  O
baked  O
cocottee  O
of  O
escargots  O
with  O
mushrooms  O
and  O
tomato  O
concasse  O
.  O

Moving  O
on  O
from  O
French  O
to  O
Italian  O
,  O
our  O
2nd  O
stop  O
brought  O
us  O
to  O
Latteria  B-ORG
Mozzarella  I-ORG
Bar  I-ORG
at  O
Duxton  B-LOC
Hill  I-LOC
.  O

The  O
trendy  O
casual  O
dining  O
trattoria  O
is  O
helmed  O
by  O
Chef  O
Beppe  O
de  O
Vito  O
.  O

We  O
were  O
treated  O
to  O
the  O
mains  O
that  O
will  O
be  O
featured  O
on  O
the  O
restaurant  O
week  O
's  O
menu  O
,  O
Grilled  B-F
Halibut  I-F
with  I-F
Saffron  I-F
Potato  I-F
and  I-F
Lobster  I-F
Sauce  I-F
and  O
Suckling  B-F
Pig  I-F
Porchetta  I-F
with  I-F
Peaches  I-F
and  I-F
Salmoriglio  I-F
.  O

The  O
last  O
course  O
of  O
the  O
tasting  O
trail  O
which  O
is  O
dessert  O
brought  O
us  O
to  O
Hashi  B-ORG
Japanese  I-ORG
Restaurant  I-ORG
which  O
is  O
helmed  O
by  O
Tadashi  O
Takahashi  O
.  O

We  O
were  O
very  O
privilege  O
to  O
have  O
the  O
Wagashi  B-F
that  O
is  O
flown  O
daily  O
from  O
Ganyuudou  O
,  O
Shizuoka  B-F
to  I-F
Hashi  I-F
which  O
is  O
a  O
traditional  O
handcrafted  O
sweets  O
and  O
desserts  O
for  O
5  O
generations  O
since  O
the  O
Meiji  O
era  O
,  O
1868  O
,  O
inheriting  O
the  O
craftmanship  O
from  O
generation  O
to  O
generation  O
.  O

5th  O
generation  O
Master  O
Wagashi  O
Chef  O
Hiromori  O
Uchida  O
keeps  O
the  O
tradition  O
of  O
handcrafting  O
to  O
shape  O
the  O
mochi  O
(  O
finely  O
milled  O
flour  O
)  O
into  O
flowers  O
,  O
such  O
as  O
cherry  O
blossom  O
,  O
chrysanthemum  O
,  O
lily  O
of  O
the  O
valley  O
,  O
and  O
peony  O
.  O

Booking  O
online  O
will  O
start  O
from11th  O
September  O
2013  O
atwww.restaurantweek.sg  O
.  O

American  O
Express  O
Cardmembers^  O
enjoy  O
exclusive  O
priority  O
booking  O
privileges  O
from  O
4  O
September  O
2013  O
before  O
booking  O
is  O
open  O
to  O
the  O
public  O
.  O

^Applicable  O
to  O
all  O
American  O
Express  O
Cards  O
issued  O
directly  O
by  O
American  O
Express  O
International  O
Inc.  O
in  O
Singapore  O
(  O
excluding  O
American  O
Express  O
Corporate  O
Cards  O
and  O
American  O
Express  O
Cards  O
issued  O
by  O
DBS  O
,  O
UOB  O
and  O
EZ  O
Link  O
Pte  O
Ltd  O
)  O


Fried  O
Oyster  O
used  O
to  O
be  O
sold  O
on  O
tricycle  O
with  O
a  O
3  O
foot  O
cast  O
iron  O
skillet  O
rested  O
above  O
a  O
makeshift  O
wood  O
fired  O
stove  O
which  O
was  O
fashioned  O
out  O
of  O
an  O
old  O
oil  O
drum  O
.  O

Since  O
street  O
hawkers  O
were  O
being  O
moved  O
to  O
hawker  O
centers  O
in  O
the  O
early  O
1970  O
as  O
part  O
of  O
the  O
government  O
's  O
street  O
hawkers  O
resettlement  O
program  O
.  O

Fried  B-F
Oyster  I-F
4.5/5  O
I  O
seldom  O
venture  O
to  O
the  O
west  O
side  O
of  O
Singapore  O
for  O
my  O
food  O
exploration  O
but  O
thanks  O
to  O
the  O
Singapore  O
Favourite  O
Food  O
2013  O
Food  O
Trail  O
I  O
got  O
to  O
visit  O
Leng  B-ORG
Kee  I-ORG
hawker  I-ORG
stall  I-ORG
at  O
Bukit  O
Timah  O
Market  O
.  O

The  O
Fried  B-F
Oyster  I-F
(  O
$  O
4  O
,  O
$  O
5  O
,  O
$  O
6  O
,  O
$  O
8  O
)  O
batter  O
mixture  O
of  O
oyster  O
juice  O
and  O
flour  O
was  O
fried  O
to  O
a  O
nice  O
crisp  O
,  O
garnished  O
with  O
cilantro  O
and  O
served  O
with  O
big  O
juicy  O
oyster  O
.  O

A  O
good  O
plate  O
of  O
fried  O
oyster  O
must  O
accompanied  O
with  O
a  O
good  O
dipping  O
sauce  O
and  O
Leng  O
Kee  O
did  O
not  O
disappoint  O
with  O
the  O
sambal  O
chilli  O
and  O
calamansi  O
juice  O
dip  O
.  O

Satay  B-F
4.2/5  O
Besides  O
the  O
delicious  O
fried  B-F
oyster  I-F
,  O
the  O
stall  O
also  O
sells  O
delectable  O
satay  B-F
and  O
chicken  B-F
wings  I-F
.  O

The  O
satay  B-F
was  O
nicely  O
grilled  O
to  O
a  O
nice  O
smoky  O
flavour  O
paired  O
with  O
the  O
peanut  O
pineapple  O
dipping  O
sauce  O
.  O

The  O
chicken  B-F
wings  I-F
were  O
also  O
beautifully  O
marinated  O
and  O
flavourful  O
.  O

Chicken  B-F
Wings  I-F
4.2/5  O
If  O
you  O
stay  O
around  O
the  O
vicinity  O
of  O
Bukit  O
Timah  O
and  O
you  O
are  O
looking  O
for  O
your  O
local  O
food  O
fix  O
,  O
I  O
would  O
recommend  O
Leng  O
Kee  O
.  O

The  O
3  O
in  O
1  O
stall  O
will  O
sure  O
to  O
satisfy  O
your  O
craving  O
with  O
its  O
delicious  O
hawker  O
fare  O
.  O

Leng  B-ORG
Kee  I-ORG
Bukit  B-LOC
Timah  I-LOC
Market  I-LOC
and  I-LOC
Food  I-LOC
Centre  I-LOC
51  I-LOC
Upper  I-LOC
Bukit  I-LOC
Timah  I-LOC
Road  I-LOC
Stall  I-LOC
144  I-LOC
Singapore  I-LOC
588215  I-LOC
Nearest  O
MRT  O
:  O
Clementi  O
(  O
EW  O
Line  O
)  O
,  O
Botanic  O
Gardens  O
(  O
CC  O
Line  O
)  O
,  O
Farrer  O
Road  O
(  O
CC  O
Line  O
)  O
Opening  O
Hours  O
:  O
Daily  O
:  O
3pm  O
to  O
11pm  O
Direction  O
:  O
1  O
)  O
Alight  O
at  O
Clementi  O
MRT  O
station  O
.  O

Take  O
Exit  O
B  O
.  O

Walk  O
to  O
bus  O
stop  O
at  O
Clementi  O
MRT  O
station  O
(  O
Stop  O
ID  O
17179  O
)  O
.  O

Take  O
bus  O
number  O
52  O
or  O
184  O
.  O

Journey  O
time  O
about  O
15  O
minutes  O
.  O

2  O
)  O
Alight  O
at  O
Botanic  O
Gardens  O
MRT  O
station  O
.  O

Take  O
Exit  O
A  O
.  O

Walk  O
to  O
bus  O
stop  O
at  O
Botanic  O
Gardens  O
MRT  O
station  O
(  O
Stop  O
ID  O
41021  O
)  O
.  O

Take  O
bus  O
number  O
66  O
,  O
67  O
,  O
170  O
or  O
171  O
.  O

Journey  O
time  O
about  O
20  O
minutes  O
.  O

3  O
)  O
Alight  O
at  O
Farrer  O
Road  O
MRT  O
station  O
.  O

Take  O
Exit  O
B  O
.  O

Walk  O
to  O
bus  O
stop  O
at  O
Farrer  O
Road  O
MRT  O
station  O
.  O

(  O
Stop  O
ID  O
11111  O
)  O
.  O

Take  O
bus  O
number  O
174  O
or  O
961  O
.  O

Journey  O
time  O
about  O
20  O
minutes  O
.  O

4  O
)  O
Alight  O
at  O
Clementi  O
MRT  O
station  O
.  O

Take  O
Exit  O
A  O
.  O

Walk  O
to  O
bus  O
interchange  O
(  O
Stop  O
ID  O
17009  O
)  O
.  O

Take  O
bus  O
173  O
.  O

Journey  O
time  O
about  O
25  O
minute  O
.  O


Located  O
on  O
the  O
rooftop  O
on  O
level  O
24  O
of  O
Hilton  O
Singapore  O
is  O
a  O
cozy  O
and  O
intimate  O
pool  O
side  O
Italian  O
restaurant  O
that  O
serves  O
nostalgic  O
flavours  O
of  O
the  O
days  O
past  O
presented  O
in  O
a  O
contemporary  O
style.Il  O
Cielo  B-ORG
Restaurant  I-ORG
(  O
means  O
``  O
The  O
Sky  O
''  O
)  O
is  O
helm  O
by  O
Italian  O
Chef  O
Omar  O
Bernardi  O
using  O
natural  O
,  O
organic  O
and  O
sustainable  O
sources  O
.  O

With  O
a  O
seating  O
capacity  O
of  O
48  O
persons  O
that  O
includes  O
indoor  O
,  O
a  O
private  O
room  O
and  O
pool  O
side  O
seating  O
comes  O
with  O
a  O
panoramic  O
view  O
of  O
Orchard  O
Road  O
skyline  O
,  O
providing  O
an  O
urban  O
resort  O
feel  O
with  O
its  O
interiors  O
and  O
surroundings  O
.  O

Bosco  B-F
(  O
$  O
45  O
for  O
whole  O
)  O
il  B-F
Cielo  I-F
Pizza  I-F
(  O
$  O
50  O
for  O
whole  O
)  O
4.2/5  O
For  O
the  O
best  O
of  O
both  O
world  O
,  O
the  O
chef  O
made  O
us  O
a  O
half  O
half  O
pizza  O
.  O

The  O
distinct  O
and  O
aromatic  O
truffle  O
from  O
can  O
be  O
smelled  O
from  O
a  O
distance  O
when  O
the  O
pizza  O
was  O
served  O
.  O

It  O
came  O
from  O
the  O
Bosco  B-F
(  O
$  O
45  O
for  O
whole  O
)  O
that  O
is  O
topped  O
with  O
porcini  O
,  O
home  O
cured  O
Italian  O
sausage  O
and  O
truffle  O
.  O

The  O
other  O
Il  B-F
Cielo  I-F
(  O
$  O
50  O
for  O
whole  O
)  O
is  O
a  O
Neapolitan  O
pizza  O
topped  O
with  O
Maine  O
lobster  O
and  O
caviar  O
.  O

Both  O
Rome  O
style  O
pizzas  O
are  O
made  O
with  O
flour  O
from  O
Vesuviana  O
that  O
were  O
thin  O
and  O
crispy  O
.  O

Burrata  B-F
4/5  O
A  O
first  O
in  O
Singapore  O
where  O
the  O
Burrata  B-F
Mozzarella  I-F
(  O
$  O
38  O
)  O
is  O
freshly  O
made  O
'a  O
la  O
minute  O
'  O
and  O
paired  O
with  O
heirloom  O
tomatoes  O
.  O

The  O
homemade  O
buffalo  O
milk  O
burrata  O
surprisingly  O
has  O
a  O
nice  O
bite  O
to  O
it  O
from  O
the  O
outer  O
layer  O
with  O
a  O
nice  O
contrasting  O
soft  O
and  O
moist  O
filled  O
bufala  O
inside  O
.  O

Capesante  B-F
4/5  O
The  O
Capesante  B-F
(  O
$  O
32  O
)  O
comes  O
with  O
a  O
trio  O
of  O
scallops  O
done  O
3  O
ways  O
.  O

We  O
have  O
the  O
pancetta  O
and  O
truffle  O
,  O
foie  O
gras  O
and  O
wine  O
reduction  O
and  O
Saffron  O
sauce  O
with  O
caviar  O
.  O

A  O
delightful  O
trio  O
to  O
sample  O
the  O
different  O
flavours  O
and  O
execution  O
from  O
the  O
chef  O
.  O

Kamut  B-F
Spaghetti  I-F
4/5  O
The  O
Spaghetti  B-F
(  O
$  O
36  O
)  O
at  O
Il  B-LOC
Cielo  I-LOC
is  O
made  O
from  O
the  O
rare  O
kamut  O
flour  O
.  O

Kamut  O
is  O
not  O
the  O
name  O
of  O
the  O
wheat  O
but  O
a  O
trademark  O
.  O

The  O
Khorasan  O
wheat  O
is  O
an  O
ancient  O
type  O
of  O
grain  O
organically  O
grown  O
,  O
believed  O
to  O
have  O
originated  O
from  O
Egypt  O
.  O

The  O
al  O
dente  O
spaghetti  O
was  O
cooked  O
with  O
sicilian  O
red  O
prawn  O
,  O
zucchini  O
and  O
caviar  O
.  O

It  O
was  O
hearty  O
and  O
homely  O
but  O
yet  O
with  O
a  O
modernised  O
execution  O
.  O

Branzino  B-F
4/5  O
The  O
Branzino  B-F
(  O
$  O
75  O
)  O
comes  O
with  O
a  O
whole  O
sea  O
bass  O
flash  O
roasted  O
on  O
olive  O
wood  O
.  O

The  O
fish  O
is  O
served  O
whole  O
and  O
deboned  O
at  O
table  O
side  O
by  O
the  O
waiter  O
.  O

The  O
sea  O
bass  O
was  O
moist  O
and  O
came  O
with  O
a  O
hint  O
of  O
earthy  O
aroma  O
.  O

Agnello  B-F
4.2/5  O
The  O
Agnello  B-F
(  O
$  O
50  O
)  O
is  O
cooked  O
to  O
medium  O
exactly  O
what  O
we  O
have  O
ordered  O
.  O

The  O
beautiful  O
olive  O
crusted  O
colorado  O
rack  O
of  O
lamb  O
was  O
beautiful  O
and  O
paired  O
with  O
excellently  O
with  O
the  O
truffle  O
mustard  O
.  O

Tortino  B-F
Al  I-F
Cioccolato  I-F
3/5  O
The  O
Tortino  B-F
Al  I-F
Cioccolata  I-F
(  O
$  O
18  O
)  O
was  O
rather  O
misleading  O
.  O

The  O
Amadel  O
Dark  O
Chocolate  O
Souffle  O
was  O
more  O
like  O
a  O
molten  O
lava  O
chocolate  O
cake  O
rather  O
than  O
a  O
souffle  O
.  O

The  O
accompanying  O
spicy  O
vanilla  O
ice  O
cream  O
on  O
the  O
other  O
was  O
rather  O
unique  O
,  O
creamy  O
and  O
smooth  O
with  O
a  O
nice  O
tad  O
of  O
spiciness  O
.  O

Overall  O
the  O
most  O
memorable  O
experience  O
is  O
the  O
cosy  O
,  O
intimate  O
and  O
alluring  O
ambience  O
of  O
the  O
restaurant  O
in  O
a  O
semi-alfresco  O
setting  O
.  O

Awarded  O
the  O
Ospitalita  O
Italiana  O
Seal  O
for  O
quality  O
,  O
authentic  O
Italian  O
cuisine  O
,  O
Il  B-ORG
Cielo  I-ORG
uses  O
the  O
finest  O
natural  O
and  O
organic  O
produce  O
including  O
seasonal  O
vegetables  O
and  O
herbs  O
,  O
sustainable  O
seafood  O
sources  O
as  O
well  O
as  O
fresh  O
and  O
natural  O
cuts  O
that  O
are  O
free  O
of  O
hormones  O
,  O
antibiotics  O
and  O
other  O
harmful  O
chemicals  O
.  O

Il  B-ORG
Cielo  I-ORG
Hilton  B-LOC
Singapore  I-LOC
Level  I-LOC
24  I-LOC
581  I-LOC
Orchard  I-LOC
Road  I-LOC
Singapore  I-LOC
238883  I-LOC
Tel  O
:  O
+65  O
67303390  O
Facebook  O
:  O
https  O
:  O
//www.facebook.com/hiltonsingapore  O
Website  O
:  O
http  O
:  O
//www3.hilton.com/en/hotels/singapore/hilton-singapore-hotel-SINHITW/dining/index.html  O
Nearest  O
MRT  O
:  O
Orchard  O
(  O
NS  O
Line  O
)  O
Opening  O
Hours  O
:  O
Mon-Fri  O
:  O
12pm  O
-  O
230pm  O
,  O
7pm  O
-  O
1030pm  O
Sat-Sun  O
:  O
7pm  O
-  O
1030pm  O
Direction  O
:  O
1  O
)  O
Alight  O
at  O
Orchard  O
MRT  O
station  O
.  O

Take  O
Exit  O
E.  O
Walk  O
towards  O
Wheelock  O
Place  O
via  O
ION  O
.  O

Exit  O
Wheelock  O
Place  O
and  O
turn  O
left  O
towards  O
Liat  O
Tower  O
.  O

Continue  O
walking  O
along  O
Orchard  O
Road  O
.  O

Journey  O
time  O
is  O
about  O
8  O
minutes  O
.  O


Award  O
winning  O
South  O
African  O
wine  O
producer  O
Nederburg  B-ORG
Wines  I-ORG
(  O
with  O
200  O
years  O
of  O
history  O
)  O
has  O
created  O
a  O
selection  O
of  O
limited  O
edition  O
,  O
home  O
made  O
gourmet  O
wines  O
known  O
as  O
Heritage  O
Heros  O
.  O

Each  O
individually  O
named  O
,  O
they  O
have  O
been  O
made  O
to  O
honour  O
some  O
of  O
the  O
major  O
figures  O
in  O
South  O
Africa  O
winemaking  O
who  O
have  O
been  O
a  O
source  O
of  O
inspiration  O
to  O
award  O
winning  O
winemaker  O
Razvan  O
Macici  O
.  O

The  O
Anchorman  B-F
-  O
Chenin  O
Blanc  O
2011  O
The  O
Anchorman  B-F
is  O
named  O
after  O
Nederburgs  O
founder  O
,  O
Philippus  O
Wolvaart  O
,  O
who  O
bought  O
the  O
farm  O
in  O
1791  O
and  O
planted  O
Chenin  O
Blanc  O
,  O
amongst  O
other  O
varietals  O
.  O

He  O
had  O
the  O
vision  O
and  O
courage  O
to  O
tame  O
a  O
wilderness  O
and  O
grow  O
great  O
wine  O
.  O

His  O
fingertips  O
are  O
still  O
on  O
every  O
wine  O
we  O
make  O
.  O

The  O
Anchorman  B-F
-  O
Chenin  O
Blanc  O
2011  O
Vineyards  O
:  O
Fruit  O
from  O
old  O
,  O
low  O
lying  O
dryland  O
bush  O
vines  O
in  O
Darling  O
,  O
Paarl  O
and  O
Durbanville  O
.  O

Colour  O
:  O
Brilliant  O
with  O
a  O
golden  O
hue  O
.  O

Bouquet  O
:  O
Reminiscent  O
of  O
ripe  O
fruits  O
,  O
especially  O
apricots  O
and  O
oranges  O
with  O
a  O
floral  O
hints  O
and  O
traces  O
of  O
raisin  O
and  O
spice  O
.  O

Palate  O
:  O
Well  O
balanced  O
,  O
fresh  O
and  O
fruity  O
with  O
a  O
beautiful  O
minerality  O
and  O
an  O
excellent  O
structure  O
.  O

The  O
Motorcycle  B-F
Marvel  I-F
-  I-F
Rhone  I-F
Style  I-F
Blend  I-F
2009  I-F
The  O
Motorcycle  B-F
Marvel  I-F
honours  O
the  O
legendary  O
winemaker  O
Gnter  O
Brzel  O
,  O
who  O
was  O
cellarmaster  O
at  O
Nederburg  O
from  O
1956  O
to  O
1989  O
.  O

He  O
played  O
a  O
leading  O
role  O
in  O
building  O
Nederburgs  O
reputation  O
as  O
the  O
most  O
awarded  O
winery  O
in  O
South  O
Africa  O

The  O
Motorcycle  B-F
Marvel  I-F
-  I-F
Rhone  I-F
Style  I-F
Blend  I-F
2009  I-F
Vineyards  O
:  O
The  O
Shiraz  O
grapes  O
were  O
sourced  O
from  O
an  O
award  O
winning  O
bock  O
of  O
trellised  O
vines  O
in  O
the  O
Philadelphia  O
area  O
while  O
the  O
Carignan  O
and  O
Grenache  O
came  O
from  O
old  O
bush  O
vines  O
in  O
Paarl  O
.  O

Colour  O
:  O
Dark  O
intense  O
red  O
Bouquet  O
:  O
An  O
abundance  O
of  O
spicy  O
,  O
peppery  O
berry  O
and  O
sweet  O
fruit  O
characters  O
.  O

Palate  O
:  O
A  O
rich  O
and  O
intense  O
,  O
full  O
bodied  O
explosion  O
of  O
flavour  O
with  O
ripe  O
and  O
silky  O
tannins  O
and  O
an  O
excellent  O
integration  O
between  O
fruit  O
and  O
wood  O
.  O

The  O
other  O
2  O
Heritage  O
Heros  O
Wines  O
which  O
I  O
have  O
not  O
get  O
to  O
try  O
is  O
The  O
Young  B-F
Airhawk  I-F
-  I-F
Sauvignon  I-F
Blanc  I-F
2012  I-F
and  O
The  O
Brew  B-F
Master  I-F
-  I-F
Bordeaux  I-F
Style  I-F
Blend  I-F
2009  I-F
.  O

Nederburgs  B-F
II  I-F
Centuries  I-F
Cabernet  I-F
Sauvignon  I-F
will  O
also  O
debut  O
in  O
Singapore  O
.  O

A  O
celebration  O
of  O
two  O
centuries  O
of  O
skill  O
,  O
tradition  O
and  O
heritage  O
,  O
II  O
Centuries  O
forms  O
the  O
apex  O
of  O
the  O
multi-tiered  O
range  O
of  O
wines  O
produced  O
by  O
Nederburg  O
.  O

All  O
single-varietal  O
wines  O
,  O
the  O
best  O
of  O
best  O
collection  O
of  O
hand-made  O
wines  O
are  O
produced  O
from  O
grapes  O
sourced  O
from  O
the  O
best  O
vines  O
within  O
top-performing  O
vineyards  O
jointly  O
identified  O
by  O
our  O
highly-skilled  O
winemaking  O
and  O
viticultural  O
teams  O
.  O

The  O
Heritage  B-F
Heroes  I-F
range  O
is  O
available  O
at  O
S  O
$  O
39  O
per  O
bottle  O
and  O
the  O
II  B-F
Centuries  I-F
Cabernet  I-F
Sauvignon  I-F
is  O
available  O
at  O
S  O
$  O
79  O
per  O
bottle  O
at  O
DFS  O
.  O

They  O
are  O
also  O
available  O
in  O
popular  O
dining  O
venues  O
and  O
hotel  O
outlets  O
.  O

Direct  O
sales  O
Auric  B-LOC
Pacific  I-LOC
Marketing  I-LOC
Pte  I-LOC
Ltd  I-LOC
General  O
Enquiries  O
Hotline  O
:  O
+65  O
6867  O
9100  O
.  O

Nederburg  O
Wines  O
Website  O
:  O
http  O
:  O
//www.nederburg.com/  O


A  O
family  O
run  O
cafe  O
,  O
L'Atelier  B-F
TiramiSu  I-F
has  O
opened  O
its  O
door  O
at  O
the  O
basement  O
of  O
The  B-LOC
Central  I-LOC
@  I-LOC
Clark  I-LOC
Quay  I-LOC
.  O

L'Atelier  B-ORG
TiramiSu  I-ORG
which  O
means  O
the  O
The  O
Tiramisu  O
workshop  O
sells  O
only  O
1  O
type  O
of  O
cakes  O
,  O
Tiramisu  O
.  O

Baked  O
freshly  O
daily  O
at  O
the  O
cafe  O
.  O
L'Atelier  B-ORG
TiramiSuis  I-ORG
probably  O
the  O
only  O
Tiramisu  O
concept  O
cafe  O
in  O
Singapore  O
.  O

Hidden  O
in  O
the  O
basement  O
of  O
The  O
Central  O
,  O
it  O
easiest  O
way  O
is  O
to  O
find  O
the  O
cafe  O
is  O
to  O
take  O
Exit  O
F  O
of  O
Clark  O
Quay  O
MRT  O
station  O
.  O

Do  O
n't  O
be  O
mislead  O
that  O
the  O
cafe  O
sells  O
only  O
the  O
usual  O
Italian  O
dessert  O
of  O
caffeine  O
,  O
mascarpone  O
cheese  O
and  O
cocoa  O
powder  O
.  O

At  O
L'Atelier  B-ORG
TiramiSu  I-ORG
,  O
they  O
have  O
infused  O
exquisite  O
flavours  O
to  O
the  O
classic  O
taste  O
of  O
tiramisu  O
creating  O
a  O
perfect  O
blend  O
of  O
exquisite  O
and  O
traditional  O
.  O

Currently  O
L'Atelier  O
offers  O
4  O
different  O
flavours  O
in  O
the  O
Classico  O
,  O
Lychee  O
,  O
Dark  O
Cherry  O
and  O
Matcha  O
.  O

Interestingly  O
,  O
L'Atelier  B-ORG
TiramSu  I-ORG
's  O
tiramisu  O
is  O
made  O
using  O
the  O
Bain-Marie  O
method  O
and  O
laced  O
with  O
different  O
liqueurs  O
.  O

Dark  B-F
Cherry  I-F
Tiramisu  I-F
4/5  O
and  O
Classico  B-F
Tiramisu  I-F
4.2/5  O
The  O
Dark  B-F
Cherry  I-F
Tiramisu  I-F
(  O
slice  O
$  O
6.80/pc  O
,  O
cake  O
$  O
48  O
)  O
is  O
laced  O
with  O
a  O
combination  O
of  O
orange  O
liqueur  O
and  O
cognac  O
.  O

It  O
has  O
a  O
strong  O
alcohol  O
bitterness  O
that  O
was  O
nicely  O
balanced  O
with  O
the  O
sweetness  O
of  O
the  O
cherry  O
.  O

It  O
has  O
a  O
much  O
stronger  O
flavour  O
compared  O
to  O
the  O
other  O
3  O
tiramsu  O
I  O
tried  O
.  O

This  O
will  O
be  O
well  O
received  O
with  O
those  O
that  O
like  O
their  O
tiramisu  O
to  O
have  O
a  O
strong  O
liqueur  O
content  O
.  O

If  O
the  O
dark  O
cherry  O
is  O
the  O
north  O
pole  O
,  O
the  O
best  O
seller  O
Classico  B-F
(  O
slice  O
$  O
6.80/pc  O
,  O
cake  O
$  O
48  O
)  O
will  O
be  O
the  O
south  O
pole  O
.  O

The  O
classic  O
tiramsu  O
was  O
light  O
,  O
smooth  O
and  O
creamy  O
coupled  O
with  O
aromatic  O
coffee  O
soaked  O
layers  O
.  O

By  O
the  O
way  O
,  O
the  O
coffee  O
used  O
to  O
make  O
their  O
tiramisu  O
is  O
from  O
Liberty  O
Coffee  O
beans  O
.  O

Matcha  B-F
Tiramisu  I-F
4.5/5  O
and  O
Lychee  B-F
Tiramisu  I-F
3.8/5  O
Matcha  B-F
Tiramisu  I-F
(  O
slice  O
$  O
6.80/pc  O
,  O
cake  O
$  O
48  O
)  O
may  O
not  O
be  O
new  O
but  O
the  O
version  O
at  O
L'Atelier  B-ORG
TiramiSu  I-ORG
is  O
laced  O
with  O
dark  O
rum  O
.  O

The  O
sweetness  O
of  O
the  O
green  O
tea  O
soaked  O
biscuit  O
together  O
with  O
the  O
creamy  O
lightness  O
of  O
the  O
cake  O
was  O
a  O
delightful  O
enjoyment  O
.  O

While  O
the  O
others  O
enjoyed  O
the  O
fruity  O
Lychee  B-F
Tiramisu  I-F
(  O
slice  O
$  O
6.80/pc  O
,  O
cake  O
$  O
48  O
)  O
which  O
is  O
laced  O
with  O
Lychee  O
liqueur  O
and  O
vodka  O
,  O
it  O
fell  O
just  O
short  O
for  O
me  O
.  O

I  O
thought  O
the  O
liqueur  O
content  O
was  O
a  O
tad  O
too  O
much  O
.  O

It  O
shadowed  O
the  O
refreshing  O
fruity  O
lychee  O
flavour  O
I  O
was  O
expecting  O
.  O

Nevertheless  O
,  O
that  O
is  O
one  O
of  O
the  O
reasons  O
why  O
there  O
are  O
different  O
flavours  O
to  O
suit  O
each  O
individual  O
's  O
palate  O
.  O

Sampling  B-F
Set  I-F
For  O
those  O
that  O
can  O
not  O
decide  O
which  O
flavours  O
to  O
go  O
for  O
,  O
you  O
may  O
want  O
to  O
check  O
out  O
the  O
Sampling  B-F
Set  I-F
(  O
$  O
15  O
)  O
.  O

The  O
sampling  O
set  O
offers  O
you  O
a  O
glimpse  O
of  O
each  O
flavours  O
before  O
deciding  O
whether  O
to  O
get  O
a  O
slice  O
or  O
the  O
whole  O
cake  O
.  O

Each  O
cake  O
measures  O
7  O
inch  O
.  O

Latte  B-F
4/5  O
Camomile  B-F
Honey  I-F
4/5  O
To  O
complement  O
with  O
the  O
delectable  O
tiramisu  O
,  O
L'Atelier  B-ORG
TiramiSu  I-ORG
also  O
offers  O
a  O
selection  O
of  O
beverage  O
.  O

For  O
caffeine  O
lovers  O
,  O
the  O
cafe  O
uses  O
a  O
blend  O
from  O
Liberty  O
Coffee  O
.  O

Non-caffeine  O
drivers  O
can  O
try  O
a  O
range  O
of  O
Latisaniere  O
Teas  O
imported  O
from  O
France  O
or  O
Arizona  O
Teas  O
from  O
America  O
.  O

We  O
tried  O
the  O
Latte  B-F
(  O
$  O
4.50  O
)  O
and  O
Camomile  B-F
Honey  I-F
(  O
$  O
3  O
)  O
.  O

Drinking  O
the  O
Camomile  O
Honey  O
Tea  O
is  O
like  O
doing  O
a  O
science  O
experiment  O
in  O
the  O
lab  O
.  O

First  O
you  O
pour  O
the  O
tea  O
from  O
the  O
150ml  O
beaker  O
into  O
the  O
glass  O
of  O
ice  O
cubes  O
made  O
from  O
the  O
tea  O
.  O

Then  O
you  O
add  O
the  O
syrup  O
from  O
the  O
50ml  O
beaker  O
to  O
the  O
glass  O
.  O

L'Atelier  B-ORG
TiramiSu  I-ORG
is  O
more  O
of  O
a  O
takeaway  O
shop  O
with  O
its  O
small  O
seating  O
capacity  O
of  O
10-12  O
people  O
.  O

If  O
you  O
decide  O
to  O
takeaway  O
,  O
the  O
packaging  O
comes  O
with  O
an  O
elegant  O
black  O
and  O
red  O
box  O
which  O
is  O
also  O
appropriate  O
as  O
a  O
gift  O
.  O

``  O
GIVEAWAY  O
-  O
5  O
X  O
Tiramisu  O
Set  O
(  O
includes  O
a  O
slice  O
of  O
cake+  O
any  O
beverage  O
)  O
''  O
(  O
Thank  O
you  O
L'Atelier  O
TiramiSu  O
for  O
the  O
giveaway  O
)  O
5  O
lucky  O
winners  O
will  O
be  O
drawn  O
to  O
win  O
the  O
Tiramisu  O
Set  O
each  O
.  O

All  O
you  O
need  O
to  O
do  O
is  O
,  O
1  O
.  O

Like  O
L'Atelier  O
TiramiSu  O
Facebook  O
page  O
.  O

Click  O
here  O
.  O

2  O
.  O

Leave  O
a  O
comment  O
that  O
you  O
have  O
like  O
the  O
L'Atelier  O
TiramiSu  O
facebook  O
and  O
tell  O
me  O
which  O
tiramisu  O
flavour  O
you  O
are  O
interested  O
to  O
try  O
here  O
.  O

3  O
.  O

Ensure  O
your  O
email  O
contact  O
detail  O
is  O
available  O
as  O
winner  O
will  O
be  O
notified  O
via  O
email  O
only  O
.  O

Closing  O
date  O
:  O
18  O
August  O
2013  O
,  O
Sunday  O
2359hr  O
Valid  O
for  O
readers  O
reside  O
in  O
Singapore  O
only  O
.  O

Winner  O
will  O
be  O
announced  O
here  O
and  O
is  O
required  O
to  O
provide  O
full  O
name  O
and  O
contact  O
number  O
for  O
redemption  O
when  O
contacted  O
.  O

A  O
new  O
winner  O
will  O
be  O
drawn  O
if  O
there  O
is  O
no  O
reply  O
within  O
3  O
days  O
.  O

Congratulations  O
to  O
the  O
5  O
lucky  O
winners  O
.  O

You  O
will  O
be  O
contacted  O
via  O
email  O
.  O

Please  O
note  O
a  O
winner  O
will  O
be  O
drawn  O
if  O
there  O
is  O
no  O
reply  O
within  O
3  O
days  O
.  O

1  O
)  O
Kai  O
Ying  O
2  O
)  O
Sophia  O
Ang  O
3  O
)  O
Madeleine  O
4  O
)  O
Athena  O
5  O
)  O
Rosemary  O

L'ATELIER  B-ORG
TiramiSu  I-ORG
The  B-LOC
Central  I-LOC
@  I-LOC
Clark  I-LOC
Quay  I-LOC
6  I-LOC
Eu  I-LOC
Tong  I-LOC
Sen  I-LOC
Street  I-LOC
#  I-LOC
B1-09  I-LOC
Singapore  I-LOC
059817  I-LOC
Tel  O
:  O
+6593898582  O
Facebook  O
:  O
https  O
:  O
//www.facebook.com/pages/LAtelier-Tiramisu/562673593776094  O
Website  O
:  O
http  O
:  O
//latelier-tiramisu.com/  O
Nearest  O
MRT  O
:  O
Clark  O
Quay  O
(  O
NE  O
Line  O
)  O
Opening  O
Hours  O
:  O
Mon-Fri  O
:  O
12pm  O
-  O
930pm  O
Sat  O
:  O
1pm  O
-  O
930pm  O
Sun  O
:  O
1pm  O
-  O
7pm  O
Direction  O
:  O
1  O
)  O
Alight  O
at  O
Clark  O
Quay  O
MRT  O
station  O
.  O

Take  O
Exit  O
F.  O
Journey  O
time  O
about  O
2  O
minutes  O
.  O

I  O
got  O
to  O
know  O
about  O
this  O
Ri  B-ORG
Ye  I-ORG
Xiang  I-ORG
Rojak  I-ORG
(  O
)  O
stall  O
because  O
of  O
the  O
Singapore  O
Favourite  O
Food  O
2013  O
-  O
Food  O
Trail  O
.  O

I  O
frequent  O
Clementi  O
but  O
has  O
never  O
noticed  O
this  O
stall  O
at  O
the  O
kopitiam  O
.  O

This  O
is  O
probably  O
the  O
oldest  O
surviving  O
rojak  O
stall  O
in  O
Singapore.With  O
48  O
years  O
of  O
history  O
since  O
1965  O
,  O
Mr  O
Edward  O
Koh  O
(  O
stall  O
owner  O
)  O
has  O
been  O
preparing  O
rojak  O
since  O
the  O
age  O
of  O
20  O
.  O

Rojak  O
which  O
means  O
mixed  O
in  O
Malay  O
is  O
a  O
dish  O
born  O
from  O
our  O
cultural  O
diversity  O
of  O
Singapore  O
incorporating  O
both  O
Chinese  O
and  O
Malay  O
elements  O
in  O
the  O
ingredients  O
.  O

Rojak  B-F
3/5  O
Ri  B-ORG 
Ye  I-ORG
Xiang  I-ORG
's  O
Rojak  B-F
is  O
the  O
savoury  O
type  O
topped  O
with  O
freshly  O
ground  O
peanut  O
which  O
Mr  O
Edward  O
Koh  O
took  O
pride  O
in  O
.  O

Also  O
known  O
as  O
the  O
Chinese  O
salad  O
,  O
it  O
comes  O
with  O
a  O
mix  O
of  O
youtiao  O
,  O
bang  O
kuang  O
,  O
pineapple  O
,  O
tau  O
pok  O
and  O
cucumbe  O
tossed  O
in  O
a  O
special  O
prawn  O
paste  O
.  O

Rojak  B-F
3/5  O
Ri  B-ORG
Ye  I-ORG 
Xiang  I-ORG 
's  O
Rojak  B-F
has  O
with  O
a  O
taste  O
of  O
tradition  O
which  O
is  O
quite  O
delectable  O
.  O

The  O
rojak  O
may  O
not  O
be  O
well  O
received  O
by  O
the  O
younger  O
generations  O
who  O
prefer  O
a  O
stronger  O
and  O
compliex  O
flavour  O
.  O

Ri  B-ORG
Ye  I-ORG
Xiang  I-ORG
Rojak  I-ORG
(  O
)  O
Kopitiam  B-LOC
Blk  I-LOC
450  I-LOC
Clementi  I-LOC
Avenue  I-LOC
3  I-LOC
Singapore  I-LOC
120450  I-LOC
Nearest  O
MRT  O
:  O
Clementi  O
(  O
EW  O
Line  O
)  O
Opening  O
Hours  O
:  O
Daily  O
:  O
3pm  O
-  O
11pm  O
Direction  O
:  O
1  O
)  O
Alight  O
at  O
Clementi  O
MRT  O
station  O
.  O

Take  O
Exit  O
A  O
.  O

Walk  O
straight  O
towards  O
CityVibe  O
and  O
continue  O
straight  O
to  O
block  O
450  O
.  O

Journey  O
time  O
about  O
3  O
minutes  O
.  O


Recently  O
I  O
have  O
been  O
going  O
to  O
The  O
Grandstand  O
and  O
I  O
always  O
noticed  O
a  O
crowd  O
at  O
the  O
Indian  O
restaurant  O
,  O
Curry  B-ORG
Garden  I-ORG
.  O

In  O
one  O
of  O
my  O
recent  O
visit  O
,  O
I  O
decided  O
to  O
check  O
it  O
out  O
since  O
the  O
restaurant  O
always  O
has  O
a  O
constant  O
flow  O
of  O
customers  O
.  O

Actually  O
I  O
was  O
quite  O
lost  O
in  O
what  O
to  O
order  O
so  O
I  O
just  O
went  O
to  O
the  O
set  O
menu  O
section  O
and  O
ordered  O
from  O
there  O
.  O

Mango  B-F
Lassi  I-F
4/5  O
While  O
waiting  O
for  O
my  O
meal  O
,  O
I  O
ordered  O
a  O
Mango  B-F
Lassi  I-F
to  O
start  O
with  O
.  O

Lassi  O
is  O
a  O
traditional  O
yogurt  O
based  O
drink  O
originating  O
from  O
India  O
.  O

The  O
mango  O
lassi  O
blended  O
with  O
yogurt  O
,  O
water  O
and  O
mango  O
pulp  O
was  O
cooling  O
,  O
soothing  O
and  O
perfect  O
compliment  O
for  O
the  O
spicy  O
food  O
.  O

Garlic  B-F
Naan  I-F
Chicken  I-F
Set  I-F
3.8/5  O
The  O
Garlic  B-F
Naan  I-F
Chicken  I-F
Set  I-F
(  O
$  O
7.50  O
)  O
comes  O
with  O
2  O
pieces  O
of  O
garlic  O
naan  O
cut  O
into  O
4  O
pieces  O
,  O
curry  O
and  O
with  O
a  O
choice  O
of  O
butter  O
chicken  O
or  O
chicken  O
tikka  O
.  O

I  O
went  O
for  O
the  O
chicken  O
tikka  O
but  O
I  O
order  O
another  O
serving  O
of  O
mutton  O
masala  O
.  O

I  O
ca  O
n't  O
resist  O
ordering  O
the  O
mutton  O
masala  O
after  O
noticing  O
the  O
next  O
table  O
having  O
it  O
.  O

The  O
chicken  O
tikka  O
was  O
too  O
dry  O
to  O
go  O
with  O
the  O
naan  O
,  O
mutton  O
masala  O
is  O
better  O
option  O
.  O

I  O
also  O
did  O
not  O
like  O
the  O
curry  O
as  O
it  O
was  O
served  O
cold  O
.  O

Batura  B-F
Set  I-F
Chicken  I-F
3.8/5  O
My  O
partner  O
ordered  O
the  O
Batura  B-F
Chicken  I-F
Set  I-F
(  O
$  O
6  O
)  O
with  O
butter  O
chicken  O
.  O

We  O
did  O
not  O
know  O
what  O
is  O
a  O
batura  O
and  O
we  O
were  O
surprised  O
to  O
see  O
the  O
huge  O
puffed  O
bread  O
made  O
from  O
maida  O
flour  O
when  O
it  O
was  O
served  O
.  O

We  O
are  O
also  O
surprised  O
that  O
the  O
butter  O
chicken  O
did  O
not  O
have  O
gravy  O
,  O
we  O
thought  O
they  O
have  O
served  O
us  O
chicken  O
tikka  O
instead  O
.  O

I  O
noticed  O
quite  O
a  O
few  O
patrons  O
ordered  O
their  O
curry  O
fish  O
head  O
,  O
I  O
should  O
try  O
to  O
have  O
them  O
in  O
my  O
next  O
visit  O
.  O

The  O
naan  O
is  O
pretty  O
good  O
too  O
but  O
I  O
will  O
prefer  O
the  O
mutton  O
masala  O
to  O
the  O
chicken  O
tikka  O
or  O
butter  O
chicken  O
.  O

Take  O
shuttle  O
bus  O
service  O
at  O
bus  O
stop  O
at  O
Exit  O
A  O
.  O

Journey  O
time  O
about  O
8  O
minutes  O
.  O


Located  O
at  O
the  O
corner  O
of  O
the  O
stretch  O
of  O
shop  O
houses  O
facing  O
the  O
main  O
road  O
at  O
Holland  O
Village  O
is  O
this  O
ode  O
charm  O
classic  O
English  O
Steakhouse  O
,  O
Fosters  B-ORG
Steakhouse  I-ORG
since  O
1960  O
.  O

Fosters  B-ORG
Steakhouse  I-ORG
was  O
first  O
established  O
at  O
25  O
Amber  O
Mansion  O
of  O
old  O
Orchard  O
.  O

Moving  O
another  O
2  O
times  O
to  O
Specialists  O
Shopping  O
Centre  O
and  O
Palais  O
Renaissance  O
before  O
settling  O
down  O
at  O
the  O
current  O
venue  O
.  O

Upon  O
settling  O
down  O
,  O
warm  O
breads  O
were  O
served  O
.  O

After  O
browsing  O
through  O
the  O
menu  O
,  O
my  O
partner  O
and  O
I  O
decided  O
to  O
go  O
for  O
the  O
lunch  B-F
set  I-F
menu  I-F
which  O
comes  O
with  O
a  O
choice  O
of  O
soup  O
,  O
mains  O
,  O
a  O
dessert  O
of  O
the  O
day  O
and  O
coffee  O
or  O
tea  O
at  O
$  O
17.90++  O
Mushroom  B-F
Soup  I-F
3.5/5  O
and  O
Onion  B-F
Soup  I-F
4/5  O
Both  O
the  O
Mushroom  B-F
Soup  I-F
and  O
Onion  B-F
Soup  I-F
were  O
comforting  O
and  O
homely  O
.  O

Compared  O
the  O
two  O
,  O
I  O
would  O
preferred  O
the  O
Onion  B-F
Soup  I-F
which  O
is  O
more  O
flavourful  O
with  O
the  O
sweetness  O
of  O
the  O
caramelised  O
onion  O
.  O

Fillet  B-F
Steak  I-F
4/5  O
There  O
were  O
5  O
choices  O
for  O
main  O
.  O

I  O
had  O
the  O
Fillet  B-F
Steak  I-F
which  O
was  O
grilled  O
tenderloin  O
served  O
with  O
chestnut  O
sauce  O
.  O

The  O
chestnut  O
sauce  O
sounds  O
interesting  O
but  O
I  O
was  O
not  O
really  O
noticeable  O
.  O

The  O
fillet  O
inself  O
was  O
tender  O
and  O
juicy  O
.  O

It  O
was  O
beautifully  O
cooked  O
.  O

Combo  B-F
Grill  I-F
3.8/5  O
Similar  O
plating  O
of  O
mash  O
potatoes  O
,  O
french  O
beans  O
and  O
carrot  O
was  O
used  O
for  O
the  O
Combo  B-F
Grill  I-F
.  O

The  O
platter  O
of  O
beef  O
steak  O
,  O
chicken  O
and  O
salmon  O
fillet  O
served  O
with  O
mushroom  O
sauce  O
was  O
value  O
for  O
money  O
.  O

While  O
the  O
beef  O
and  O
chicken  O
were  O
tender  O
and  O
succulent  O
,  O
the  O
salmon  O
was  O
a  O
bit  O
over  O
cooked  O
and  O
dry  O
.  O

Coffee  B-F
The  O
lunch  O
set  O
menu  O
comes  O
with  O
a  O
choice  O
of  O
Coffee  B-F
or  O
Tea  B-F
.  O

We  O
are  O
both  O
coffee  O
drinker  O
so  O
inevitable  O
our  O
choice  O
is  O
not  O
quite  O
difficult  O
.  O

Apple  B-F
Strudel  I-F
with  I-F
Vanilla  I-F
Ice  I-F
Cream  I-F
3/5  O
The  O
dessert  O
of  O
the  O
day  O
was  O
Apple  B-F
Strudel  I-F
with  I-F
Vanilla  I-F
Ice  I-F
Cream  I-F
.  O

A  O
simple  O
sweet  O
ending  O
for  O
lunch  O
.  O

While  O
dining  O
at  O
the  O
restaurant  O
,  O
I  O
noticed  O
there  O
were  O
many  O
awards  O
and  O
write  O
ups  O
being  O
framed  O
and  O
hanged  O
on  O
the  O
walls  O
.  O

It  O
seems  O
like  O
Fosters  B-ORG
Steakhouse  I-ORG
is  O
quite  O
renowned  O
for  O
serving  O
quality  O
and  O
delish  O
steak  O
and  O
great  O
rendition  O
of  O
the  O
English  O
classics  O
.  O

While  O
the  O
lunch  O
set  O
is  O
value  O
for  O
money  O
,  O
I  O
look  O
forward  O
to  O
try  O
their  O
ala  O
carte  O
menu  O
in  O
my  O
next  O
wish  O
.  O

Fosters  B-ORG
Steakhouse  I-ORG
Holland  B-LOC
Village  I-LOC
277  I-LOC 
Holland   I-LOC
Ave  I-LOC
Singapore  I-LOC
278994  I-LOC
Tel  O
:  O
+65  O
64668939  O
Website  O
:  O
http  O
:  O
//www.fosters-restaurant.com/  O
Nearest  O
MRT  O
:  O
Holland  O
Village  O
(  O
CC  O
Line  O
)  O
Opening  O
Hours  O
:  O
Daily  O
:  O
11am  O
-  O
11pm  O
Direction  O
:  O
1  O
)  O
Alight  O
at  O
Holland  O
Village  O
MRT  O
station  O
.  O

Take  O
Exit  O
B  O
.  O

At  O
the  O
exit  O
,  O
turn  O
right  O
and  O
walk  O
to  O
the  O
end  O
of  O
the  O
shop  O
houses  O
.  O

Journey  O
time  O
about  O
3  O
minutes  O
.  O


A  O
month  O
has  O
flown  O
by  O
and  O
its  O
Makansutra  B-ORG
dinner  I-ORG
for  O
the  O
month  O
of  O
July  O
2013  O
.  O

This  O
time  O
the  O
dinner  O
was  O
at  O
The  O
Grandstand  O
and  O
its  O
my  O
first  O
Japanese  O
makansutra  O
dinner  O
.  O

I  O
am  O
glad  O
that  O
besides  O
the  O
regulars  O
,  O
we  O
have  O
Karen  O
,  O
Philip  O
and  O
Serene  O
joining  O
us  O
this  O
time  O
.  O

Pitan  B-F
Tofu  I-F
4.2/5  O
As  O
usual  O
dinner  O
started  O
quite  O
late  O
at  O
8pm  O
.  O

We  O
started  O
the  O
10  O
course  O
meal  O
with  O
Pitan  B-F
Tofu  I-F
.  O

It  O
reminded  O
me  O
of  O
the  O
same  O
dish  O
I  O
had  O
many  O
years  O
ago  O
which  O
brought  O
back  O
many  O
memories  O
.  O

Enhanced  O
by  O
the  O
century  O
egg  O
,  O
the  O
combination  O
was  O
a  O
delightful  O
enjoyment  O
of  O
texture  O
and  O
flavour  O
.  O

Nama  B-F
Kaki  I-F
Ponzu  I-F
4.2/5  O
The  B-F
Fin  I-F
De  I-F
Claire  I-F
Oyster  I-F
with  I-F
Ponzu  I-F
Sauce  I-F
was  O
fresh  O
and  O
bursting  O
with  O
the  O
delightful  O
flavours  O
of  O
the  O
sea  O
.  O

Fugu  B-F
Mirin  I-F
Boshi  I-F
4/5  O
When  O
the  O
Fugu  B-F
Mirin  I-F
Boshi  I-F
was  O
served  O
,  O
everyone  O
at  O
the  O
table  O
was  O
trying  O
to  O
guess  O
what  O
it  O
is  O
?  O

The  O
taste  O
and  O
texture  O
which  O
resembles  O
the  O
Bak  O
Kwa  O
is  O
actually  O
dried  O
puffer  O
fish  O
seasoned  O
with  O
sweet  O
sake  O
.  O

It  O
is  O
a  O
tradtional  O
snack  O
eaten  O
while  O
drinking  O
sake  O
.  O

I  O
have  O
tried  O
the  O
dried  O
puffer  O
fish  O
before  O
in  O
my  O
previous  O
experience  O
at  O
Seki  O
Japanese  O
Restaurant  O
which  O
unfortunately  O
has  O
closed  O
its  O
door  O
.  O

Sashimi  B-F
Moriawase  I-F
4/5  O
The  O
Sashimi  B-F
Moriawase  I-F
was  O
served  O
with  O
6  O
kinds  O
of  O
fresh  O
sashimi  O
.  O

Among  O
the  O
assorted  O
sashimi  O
,  O
I  O
thought  O
the  O
squid  O
with  O
stuffed  O
roe  O
was  O
interesting  O
with  O
a  O
nice  O
crunchy  O
bite  O
that  O
came  O
with  O
popping  O
surprises  O
.  O

Tenderloin  B-F
Teppanyaki  I-F
4.5/5  O
The  O
Tenderloin  B-F
Teppanyaki  I-F
was  O
probably  O
the  O
highlight  O
of  O
the  O
night  O
.  O

The  O
Australian  O
beef  O
with  O
homemade  O
apple  O
sauce  O
was  O
pan  O
fried  O
to  O
perfection  O
.  O

The  O
beef  O
was  O
tender  O
and  O
juicy  O
bursting  O
with  O
flavours  O
.  O

Makimono  B-F
Moriawase  I-F
3/5  O
The  O
Makimono  B-F
Moriawase  I-F
was  O
a  O
welcome  O
trio  O
of  O
carbohydrates  O
to  O
satisfy  O
the  O
hungry  O
stomach  O
.  O

Ebi  B-F
Kawari  I-F
Mayonnaise  I-F
Ae  I-F
4.2/5  O
The  O
Ebi  B-F
Kawari  I-F
Maonnaise  I-F
Ae  O
was  O
another  O
lovely  O
dish  O
.  O

The  O
marinated  O
prawn  O
fritters  O
was  O
crunchy  O
and  O
coated  O
in  O
a  O
delectable  O
garlic  O
sauce  O
.  O

Toro  B-F
no  I-F
Foie  I-F
Gras  I-F
Miso  I-F
Yaki  I-F
3.5/5  O
This  O
is  O
the  O
dish  O
that  O
everyone  O
was  O
looking  O
forward  O
to  O
but  O
the  O
Toro  B-F
no  I-F
Foie  I-F
Gras  I-F
Miso  I-F
Yaki  I-F
was  O
a  O
bit  O
of  O
a  O
disappointment  O
.  O

The  O
flavours  O
were  O
excellent  O
individually  O
.  O

However  O
the  O
fatty  O
tuna  O
was  O
overpowered  O
by  O
the  O
strong  O
flavours  O
of  O
the  O
duck  O
meat  O
,  O
duck  O
liver  O
and  O
miso  O
sauce  O
when  O
eaten  O
together  O
.  O

The  O
texture  O
of  O
the  O
wheat  O
noodle  O
was  O
lumpy  O
and  O
chewy  O
that  O
was  O
not  O
enjoyable  O
.  O

Jus  B-F
Alpukat  I-F
4/5  O
Lunch  O
was  O
served  O
with  O
a  O
complimentary  O
plate  O
of  O
keropok  O
.  O

I  O
like  O
that  O
they  O
have  O
a  O
varieties  O
of  O
it  O
however  O
inside  O
me  O
was  O
screaming  O
for  O
a  O
chilli  O
dip  O
to  O
go  O
with  O
it  O
.  O

The  O
fork  O
tender  O
beef  O
redang  O
was  O
slow  O
cooked  O
for  O
at  O
least  O
4  O
hours  O
packed  O
with  O
richness  O
of  O
the  O
spices  O
.  O

Nevertheless  O
the  O
chicken  O
was  O
cooked  O
perfectly  O
,  O
tender  O
and  O
moist  O
.  O

The  O
thick  O
and  O
yet  O
clear  O
broth  O
was  O
comforting  O
and  O
hearty  O
.  O

Take  O
bus  O
number  O
75  O
or  O
970  O
.  O

Take  O
bus  O
number  O
5  O
,  O
16  O
or  O
195  O
.  O

Take  O
bus  O
number  O
16  O
or  O
175  O
.  O

Alight  O
4  O
bus  O
stops  O
later  O
.  O

Journey  O
time  O
about  O
12  O
minutes  O
.  O


For  O
the  O
month  O
of  O
August  O
to  O
September  O
2013  O
,  O
10  B-ORG
at  I-ORG
Claymore  I-ORG
at  O
Pan  O
Pacific  O
Orchard  O
will  O
be  O
bringing  O
back  O
timeless  O
classic  O
dishes  O
featuring  O
preparation  O
methods  O
of  O
the  O
60  O
's  O
and  O
70  O
's  O
.  O

Themed  O
Timeless  O
Plates  O
of  O
Pleasure  O
,  O
let  O
us  O
embark  O
a  O
food  O
trail  O
down  O
memory  O
lane  O
when  O
flavours  O
were  O
simple  O
yet  O
hearty  O
.  O

At  O
10  B-ORG
at  I-ORG
Claymore  I-ORG
,  O
one  O
will  O
be  O
spoiled  O
for  O
choices  O
as  O
you  O
get  O
to  O
order  O
from  O
the  O
ala  O
carte  O
buffet  O
menu  O
as  O
well  O
as  O
extensive  O
selections  O
of  O
international  O
cuisines  O
of  O
seafood  O
,  O
cooked  O
food  O
and  O
desserts  O
spread  O
around  O
the  O
spacious  O
restaurant  O
.  O

Canadian  B-F
Handpicked  I-F
Scallop  I-F
2.8/5  O
Ordering  O
from  O
the  O
ala  O
carte  O
buffet  O
menu  O
,  O
we  O
started  O
with  O
the  O
Canadian  B-F
Handpicked  I-F
Scallop  I-F
.  O

It  O
is  O
prepared  O
like  O
a  O
yam  O
basket  O
with  O
the  O
scallop  O
inside  O
topped  O
with  O
Imperial  O
XO  O
sauce  O
.  O

Interesting  O
concept  O
but  O
individual  O
flavours  O
felt  O
disjoint  O
.  O

Pacific  B-F
Ocean  I-F
Depth  I-F
Sea  I-F
Perch  I-F
3.5/5  O
The  O
Pacific  B-F
Ocean  I-F
Depth  I-F
Sea  I-F
Perch  I-F
fared  O
much  O
better  O
with  O
the  O
Chong  O
Qing  O
spiced  O
bean  O
gravy  O
enhancing  O
the  O
flavours  O
of  O
the  O
fresh  O
and  O
moist  O
fish  O
.  O

Australian  B-F
Master  I-F
Kobe  I-F
Wagyu  I-F
Beef  I-F
'Outside  I-F
Flat  I-F
'  I-F
4.2/5  O
Cooked  O
beautifully  O
with  O
mushroom  O
creme  O
,  O
the  O
Australian  B-F
Master  I-F
Kobe  I-F
Wagyu  I-F
Beef  I-F
'Outside  I-F
Flat  I-F
'  I-F
was  O
flavourful  O
and  O
succulent  O
.  O

New  B-F
Zealand  I-F
Free  I-F
Range  I-F
Lamb  I-F
Shank  I-F
4/5  O
The  O
melted  O
in  O
the  O
mouth  O
New  B-F
Zealand  I-F
Free  I-F
Range  I-F
Lamb  I-F
Shank  I-F
with  O
Shiraz  O
Reduction  O
is  O
worth  O
putting  O
on  O
a  O
few  O
pounds  O
for  O
it  O
.  O

Indo-China  B-F
Farmed  I-F
Duck  I-F
Breast  I-F
4/5  O
While  O
others  O
find  O
the  O
Indo-China  B-F
Farmed  I-F
Duck  I-F
Breast  I-F
gamey  O
,  O
I  O
thought  O
the  O
pinkish  O
sliced  O
duck  O
breast  O
was  O
excellently  O
executed  O
.  O

The  O
citrus  O
honey  O
glaze  O
did  O
bring  O
a  O
nice  O
contrast  O
of  O
the  O
flavours  O
but  O
I  O
preferred  O
a  O
little  O
more  O
reduction  O
of  O
it  O
for  O
the  O
meat  O
to  O
shine  O
.  O

Penang  B-F
Spicy  I-F
Prawn  I-F
Noodle  I-F
in  I-F
Soup  I-F
3.5/5  O
Known  O
for  O
its  O
Penang  O
fare  O
,  O
the  O
Penang  B-F
Spicy  I-F
Prawn  I-F
Noodle  I-F
in  O
a  O
spicy  O
crustacean  O
broth  O
was  O
indeed  O
hearty  O
and  O
comforting  O
.  O

The  O
ala  O
carte  O
buffet  O
menu  O
items  O
are  O
served  O
in  O
petite  O
portions  O
so  O
diners  O
can  O
have  O
a  O
try  O
of  O
everything  O
.  O

It  O
is  O
unlimited  O
so  O
if  O
you  O
like  O
a  O
particular  O
dish  O
,  O
just  O
order  O
again  O
.  O

For  O
those  O
that  O
has  O
a  O
huge  O
appetite  O
,  O
a  O
wide  O
spread  O
of  O
succulent  O
seafood  O
and  O
bistro  O
fare  O
invites  O
you  O
at  O
the  O
buffet  O
line  O
.  O

For  O
cheese  O
lovers  O
,  O
its  O
worth  O
checking  O
out  O
the  O
cheese  O
section  O
.  O

10  B-ORG
at  I-ORG
Claymore  I-ORG
has  O
quite  O
an  O
interesting  O
cheese  O
selection  O
such  O
as  O
Stout  B-F
Porter  I-F
,  O
Stripey  B-F
Jack  I-F
,  O
Lime  B-F
&  I-F
Chilli  I-F
and  O
Cranberry  B-F
.  O

Penang  B-F
Char  I-F
Kway  I-F
Teow  I-F
4.5/5  O
Even  O
with  O
a  O
bloated  O
stomach  O
,  O
I  O
still  O
tried  O
to  O
save  O
some  O
space  O
for  O
the  O
award  O
winning  O
Penang  B-F
Char  I-F
Kway  I-F
Teow  I-F
.  O

I  O
could  O
smell  O
the  O
fragrant  O
noodle  O
from  O
a  O
distance  O
and  O
each  O
mouthful  O
was  O
filled  O
with  O
delightful  O
wok  O
hei  O
flavour  O
.  O

Dessert  O
A  O
meal  O
is  O
never  O
complete  O
without  O
dessert  O
.  O

The  O
sweet  O
tooth  O
will  O
be  O
joy  O
with  O
the  O
sweetness  O
that  O
is  O
available  O
at  O
the  O
buffet  O
spread  O
.  O

Celebrating  O
Singapore  O
48th  O
Birthday  O
this  O
year  O
,  O
diners  O
will  O
get  O
an  O
exclusive  O
price  O
of  O
$  O
48++  O
per  O
person  O
at  O
10  O
at  O
Claymore  O
on  O
the  O
8th  O
and  O
9th  O
of  O
August  O
2013  O
.  O

TimelessPlates  O
of  O
Pleasure  O
Date  O
:  O
August  O
to  O
September  O
2013  O
Dinner  O
(  O
8th  O
&  O
9th  O
August  O
)  O
:  O
$  O
48++  O
Diner  O
(  O
Mon  O
-  O
Thu  O
)  O
:  O
$  O
59++  O
Dinner  O
(  O
Fri  O
-  O
Sun  O
)  O
:  O
$  O
62++  O
Brunch  O
(  O
Sun  O
)  O
:  O
$  O
68++  O
10  B-ORG
at  I-ORG
Claymore  I-ORG
Pan  B-LOC
Pacific  I-LOC
Orchard  I-LOC
10  I-LOC
Claymore  I-LOC
Road  I-LOC
Singapore  I-LOC
229540  I-LOC
Tel  O
:  O
+65  O
67370811  O
Facebook  O
:  O
https  O
:  O
//www.facebook.com/PanPacificOrchard  O
Website  O
:  O
http  O
:  O
//www.panpacific.com/en/Orchard/Overview.html  O
Nearest  O
MRT  O
:  O
Orchard  O
(  O
NS  O
Line  O
)  O
Opening  O
Hours  O
:  O
Daily  O
:  O
6am  O
-  O
1030am  O
(  O
breakfast  O
)  O
,  O
12pm  O
-  O
230pm  O
(  O
lunch  O
)  O
,  O
6pm  O
-1030pm  O
(  O
dinner  O
)  O
Sunday  O
:  O
12pm  O
-  O
3pm  O
(  O
brunch  O
)  O
Direction  O
:  O
1  O
)  O
Alight  O
at  O
Orchard  O
MRT  O
station  O
.  O

Take  O
Exit  O
E.  O
Walk  O
towards  O
Wheellock  O
Place  O
via  O
ION  O
.  O

Exit  O
Wheellock  O
Place  O
and  O
turn  O
left  O
towards  O
Liat  O
Tower  O
.  O

Cross  O
the  O
road  O
at  O
the  O
traffic  O
light  O
junction  O
and  O
turn  O
left  O
towards  O
Royal  O
Thai  O
Embassy  O
.  O

Walk  O
to  O
Palais  O
Renaissance  O
which  O
is  O
right  O
after  O
Royal  O
Thai  O
Embassy  O
.  O

Cut  O
through  O
Palais  O
Renaissance  O
to  O
the  O
other  O
side  O
of  O
the  O
building  O
.  O

Pan  O
Pacific  O
Orchard  O
is  O
opposite  O
the  O
building  O
.  O

Journey  O
time  O
about  O
10  O
minutes  O
.  O

Take  O
Exit  O
A  O
.  O

Walk  O
towards  O
Shaw  O
House  O
via  O
underpass  O
.  O

At  O
the  O
road  O
level  O
,  O
walk  O
along  O
Orchard  O
Road  O
towards  O
Royal  O
Thai  O
Embassy  O
direction  O
.  O

Walk  O
to  O
Palais  O
Renaissance  O
which  O
is  O
right  O
after  O
Royal  O
Thai  O
Embassy  O
.  O

Cut  O
through  O
Palais  O
Renaissance  O
to  O
the  O
other  O
side  O
of  O
the  O
building  O
.  O

Pan  O
Pacific  O
Orchard  O
is  O
right  O
opposite  O
the  O
building  O
.  O

Journey  O
time  O
about  O
10  O
minutes  O
.  O


Mentioned  O
chilled  O
beancurd  O
,  O
many  O
may  O
think  O
of  O
Lao  O
Ban  O
,  O
51  O
Beancurd  O
or  O
QQ  O
Beancurd  O
.  O

Not  O
familiar  O
to  O
a  O
lot  O
of  O
people  O
is O
AmaSoy B-ORG
including  O
myself  O
.  O

I  O
was  O
only  O
introduced  O
to  O
it  O
during  O
one  O
of  O
my  O
visit  O
toDARNO  O
Japanese  O
Hotpot  O
by  O
MOF  O
.  O

There  O
are  O
dual  O
meaning  O
to  O
the  O
brand  O
name  O
,  O
Ama  O
means  O
Sweet  O
in  O
Japanese  O
and  O
also  O
Grandma  O
in  O
Chinese  O
.  O

The  O
founder  O
chanced  O
upon  O
this  O
delicious  O
Tounyu  O
Soy  O
Beancurd  O
reminiscent  O
the  O
Singapore  O
soy  O
beancurd  O
during  O
her  O
stay  O
in  O
Japan  O
and  O
the  O
taste  O
reminded  O
her  O
of  O
the  O
memories  O
when  O
she  O
was  O
growing  O
up  O
with  O
her  O
grandma  O
in  O
meager  O
conditions  O
.  O

Let  O
me  O
let  O
you  O
in  O
into  O
something  O
you  O
probably  O
did  O
not  O
know  O
too  O
.  O

AmaSoy  O
beancurd  O
recipe  O
is  O
actually  O
a  O
Japanese  O
recipe  O
which  O
is  O
more  O
natural  O
compared  O
to  O
some  O
of  O
the  O
brands  O
that  O
uses  O
coffeemix  O
in  O
the  O
mixture  O
.  O

The  O
natural  O
and  O
nutritious  O
recipe  O
is  O
trans-fat  O
free  O
,  O
no  O
cholesterol  O
,  O
low  O
fat  O
content  O
,  O
lactose  O
free  O
,  O
no  O
colouring  O
,  O
no  O
preservatives  O
or  O
MSG  O
,  O
no  O
artificial  O
flavouring  O
,  O
no  O
animal  O
gelatin  O
used  O
and  O
100  O
%  O
organic  O
soy  O
bean  O
is  O
used  O
.  O

Recently  O
,  O
AmaSoy  O
has  O
improved  O
in  O
their  O
recipes  O
enhancing  O
the  O
Japanese  O
pudding  O
with  O
Collagen  O
and  O
Omega  O
3  O
(  O
DHA  O
)  O
.  O

Besides  O
the  O
popular  O
Original  O
,  O
Almond  O
and  O
Mango  O
beancurd  O
,  O
exciting  O
new  O
flavours  O
and  O
toppings  O
are  O
introduced  O
.  O

More  O
choices  O
and  O
selections  O
now  O
.  O

New  O
flavours  O
include  O
Matcha  B-F
and  O
Salted  B-F
Caramel  I-F
.  O

For  O
toppings  O
,  O
one  O
can  O
look  O
forward  O
to  O
new  O
additions  O
such  O
as  O
red  O
bean  O
,  O
peanuts  O
,  O
gingko  O
nuts  O
,  O
lotus  O
seeds  O
,  O
aloe  O
vera  O
,  O
taro  O
and  O
strawberry  O
etc  O
.  O

So  O
why  O
do  O
I  O
prefer  O
AmaSoy  O
Japanese  O
pudding  O
or  O
beancurd  O
to  O
the  O
other  O
brand  O
?  O

First  O
of  O
all  O
,  O
I  O
find  O
the  O
other  O
brands  O
too  O
sweet  O
to  O
my  O
liking  O
.  O

AmaSoy  B-F
beancurd  I-F
is  O
not  O
too  O
sweet  O
and  O
nicely  O
balanced  O
in  O
texture  O
.  O

Have  O
you  O
ever  O
left  O
your  O
Lao  O
Ban  O
beancurd  O
overnight  O
and  O
noticed  O
a  O
sheet  O
like  O
layer  O
thingy  O
on  O
the  O
surface  O
?  O

If  O
felt  O
so  O
artificial  O
in  O
what  O
I  O
was  O
consuming  O
.  O

While  O
the  O
texture  O
of  O
Amasoy  O
may  O
not  O
be  O
as  O
smooth  O
compared  O
to  O
the  O
other  O
brands  O
,  O
the  O
health  O
conscious  O
me  O
prefer  O
the  O
all  O
natural  O
and  O
nutritious  O
recipe  O
.  O

Furthermore  O
,  O
it  O
now  O
comes  O
with  O
collagen  O
and  O
omega  O
3  O
(  O
DHA  O
)  O
.  O

Last  O
but  O
not  O
least  O
,  O
it  O
is  O
the  O
only  O
beancurd  O
brand  O
that  O
allows  O
one  O
to  O
add  O
toppings  O
of  O
their  O
liking  O
for  O
a  O
wholesome  O
enjoyment  O
of  O
this  O
delectable  O
dessert  O
.  O

With  O
the  O
new  O
revamped  O
recipe  O
and  O
menu  O
,  O
also  O
do  O
check  O
out  O
the  O
newly  O
launched  O
Hokkaido  O
Milk  O
series  O
at  O
AmaSoy  O
outlets  O
.  O

Currently  O
MOF  O
has  O
five  O
outlets  O
around  O
the  O
island  O
at  O
Great  B-LOC
World  I-LOC
City  I-LOC
,  O
Ion  B-LOC
Orchard  I-LOC
,  O
Serangoon  B-LOC
Nex  I-LOC
,  O
Jurong  B-LOC
Point  I-LOC
and  O
Tampines  B-LOC
One  I-LOC
.  O

AmaSoy  O
Delectable  O
Organic  O
Japanese  O
Beancurd  O
Website  O
:  O
http  O
:  O
//ministryoffood.com.sg/  O
?  O
ForceFlash=true  O
#  O
/submenu/BRAND-STORY_1022.html  O
Facebook  O
:  O
https  O
:  O
//www.facebook.com/AmaSoySG  O


My  O
partner  O
was  O
telling  O
about  O
this  O
hawker  O
stall  O
at  O
Changi  O
Village  O
Food  O
Centre  O
that  O
was  O
featured  O
in  O
some  O
food  O
variety  O
stall  O
that  O
sells  O
quite  O
awesome  O
sambal  O
fish  O
head  O
.  O

Some  O
on  O
a  O
Sunday  O
a  O
couple  O
of  O
weeks  O
back  O
,  O
we  O
made  O
our  O
way  O
to  O
the  O
far  O
east  O
of  O
the  O
island  O
to  O
check  O
out  O
Guang  B-ORG
Xing  I-ORG
Original  I-ORG
Taste  I-ORG
Fish  I-ORG
Head  I-ORG
Been  I-ORG
Hoon  I-ORG
(  O
)  O
stall  O
at  O
Changi  B-LOC
Village  I-LOC
Food  I-LOC
Centre  I-LOC
.  O

A  O
long  O
queue  O
was  O
formed  O
at  O
the  O
stall  O
and  O
we  O
have  O
to  O
wait  O
up  O
for  O
a  O
good  O
45  O
minutes  O
for  O
our  O
food  O
.  O

Sambal  B-F
Fish  I-F
Head  I-F
4.2/5  O
The  O
Sambal  B-F
Fish  I-F
Head  I-F
(  O
$  O
10/15/20  O
)  O
is  O
the  O
reason  O
why  O
we  O
have  O
made  O
the  O
journey  O
to  O
the  O
far  O
east  O
.  O

This  O
fiery  O
looking  O
dish  O
packed  O
a  O
punch  O
and  O
will  O
set  O
your  O
mouth  O
on  O
fire  O
.  O

I  O
am  O
not  O
sure  O
what  O
species  O
of  O
fish  O
the  O
stall  O
used  O
but  O
it  O
was  O
firm  O
and  O
bouncy  O
.  O

The  O
sambal  O
was  O
definitely  O
the  O
highlight  O
cooked  O
with  O
the  O
delectable  O
fish  O
head  O
and  O
bitter  O
gourd  O
.  O

The  O
aroma  O
sambal  O
also  O
has  O
a  O
hint  O
of  O
Hua  O
Tiao  O
wine  O
making  O
it  O
more  O
fragrant  O
.  O

The  O
stall  O
is  O
also  O
popular  O
for  O
its  O
Black  O
Bean  O
Sauce  O
Fish  O
Head  O
with  O
bitter  O
gourd  O
.  O

Fish  B-F
Soup  I-F
4.2/5  O
It  O
was  O
a  O
blessing  O
that  O
we  O
ordered  O
the  O
Fish  B-F
Soup  I-F
(  O
$  O
4  O
)  O
from  O
the  O
stall  O
too  O
.  O

It  O
helped  O
to  O
cool  O
off  O
the  O
burning  O
tongue  O
.  O

The  O
fish  O
soup  O
was  O
light  O
,  O
refreshing  O
and  O
flavourful  O
.  O

The  O
fish  O
slices  O
was  O
also  O
fresh  O
and  O
moist  O
.  O

Guang  B-ORG
Xing  I-ORG
Original  I-ORG
Taste  I-ORG
Fish  I-ORG
Head  I-ORG
Bee  I-ORG
Hoon  I-ORG
(  O
)  O
Changi  B-LOC
Village  I-LOC
Food  I-LOC
Centre  I-LOC
Stall  I-LOC
#  I-LOC
01-31  I-LOC
Blk  I-LOC
2  I-LOC
Changi  I-LOC
Village  I-LOC
Road  I-LOC
Singapore  I-LOC
500002  I-LOC
Nearest  O
MRT  O
:  O
Pasir  O
Ris  O
(  O
EW  O
Line  O
)  O
,  O
Tampines  O
(  O
EW  O
Line  O
)  O
,  O
Simei  O
(  O
EW  O
Line  O
)  O
,  O
Tanah  O
Merah  O
(  O
EW  O
Line  O
)  O
Opening  O
Hours  O
:  O
N/A  O
Direction  O
:  O
1  O
)  O
Alight  O
at  O
Pasir  O
Ris  O
MRT  O
station  O
.  O

Take  O
Exit  O
A  O
.  O

Walk  O
to  O
bus  O
stop  O
along  O
Pasir  O
Ris  O
Central  O
,  O
opposite  O
Pasir  O
Ris  O
Town  O
Park  O
(  O
Stop  O
ID  O
77171  O
)  O
.  O

Take  O
bus  O
number  O
89  O
.  O

Alight  O
17  O
stops  O
later  O
.  O

Journey  O
time  O
about  O
20  O
minutes  O
.  O

2  O
)  O
Alight  O
at  O
Tampines  O
MRT  O
station  O
.  O

Take  O
Exit  O
A  O
.  O

Walk  O
to  O
Tampines  O
Bus  O
Interchange  O
(  O
Stop  O
ID  O
75009  O
)  O
.  O

Take  O
bus  O
number  O
19  O
.  O

Journey  O
time  O
about  O
25  O
minutes  O
.  O

3  O
)  O
Alight  O
at  O
Simei  O
MRT  O
station  O
.  O

Take  O
Exit  O
A  O
.  O

Walk  O
to  O
bus  O
stop  O
at  O
Simei  O
MRT  O
station  O
(  O
Stop  O
ID  O
96169  O
)  O
.  O

Take  O
bus  O
number  O
9  O
.  O

Alight  O
19  O
stops  O
later  O
.  O

Journey  O
time  O
about  O
25  O
minutes  O
4  O
)  O
Alight  O
at  O
Tanah  O
Merah  O
MRT  O
station  O
.  O

Take  O
Exit  O
B  O
.  O

Walk  O
to  O
bus  O
stop  O
along  O
Upper  O
Changi  O
Road  O
(  O
Stop  O
ID  O
85091  O
)  O
.  O

Take  O
bus  O
number  O
2  O
.  O

Alight  O
27  O
stops  O
later  O
.  O

Journey  O
time  O
about  O
30  O
minutes  O
.  O


All  O
these  O
while  O
I  O
have  O
read  O
good  O
reviews  O
on  O
Prego  B-ORG
at  O
Fairmont  B-LOC
Singapore  I-LOC
but  O
I  O
have  O
never  O
get  O
the  O
chance  O
to  O
try  O
the  O
food  O
until  O
a  O
couple  O
of  O
weeks  O
back  O
.  O

With  O
a  O
new  O
look  O
menu  O
to  O
enhance  O
the  O
dining  O
experience  O
at  O
the  O
Italian  O
Trattoria  O
,  O
Chef  O
Antonio  O
Facchinetti  O
brings  O
to  O
diner  O
an  O
authentic  O
,  O
traditional  O
and  O
homely  O
Italian  O
cuisine  O
with  O
the  O
fresh  O
and  O
quality  O
ingredients  O
.  O

We  O
started  O
the  O
meal  O
with  O
a  O
selection  O
of  O
bread  O
accompanied  O
by  O
seasonal  O
dips  O
.  O

From  O
left  O
to  O
right  O
,  O
we  O
have  O
the  O
Tomato  B-F
with  I-F
Basil  I-F
,  O
Caramelized  B-F
Onion  I-F
with  I-F
Ricotta  I-F
Cheese  I-F
and  O
Truffle  B-F
with  I-F
Ricotta  I-F
Cheese  I-F
.  O

My  O
personal  O
favourite  O
among  O
the  O
three  O
is  O
the  O
caramelized  O
onion  O
with  O
ricotta  O
cheese  O
.  O

The  O
sweet  O
and  O
savoury  O
combination  O
worked  O
wonderfully  O
with  O
the  O
caramelized  O
onions  O
lending  O
a  O
delectable  O
bite  O
.  O

Insalata  B-F
Mista  I-F
3/5  O
The  O
Insalata  B-F
Mista  I-F
(  O
$  O
19  O
)  O
is  O
a  O
mix  O
of  O
green  O
salad  O
,  O
radicchio  O
,  O
fennel  O
,  O
red  O
onion  O
and  O
lemon  O
dressing  O
.  O

While  O
I  O
appreciated  O
the  O
fresh  O
greens  O
,  O
I  O
still  O
prefer  O
a  O
little  O
more  O
of  O
the  O
zesty  O
lemon  O
dressing  O
to  O
live  O
up  O
the  O
bowl  O
of  O
salad  O
.  O

Stracciatell  B-F
di  I-F
Bufala  I-F
4.5/5  O
The  O
Stracciatell  B-F
di  I-F
Bufala  I-F
(  O
$  O
26  O
)  O
comes  O
with  O
a  O
marinated  O
king  O
prawn  O
topped  O
with  O
tomato  O
,  O
oregano  O
and  O
spring  O
onions  O
sitting  O
on  O
a  O
bed  O
of  O
buffalo  O
stracciatella  O
.  O

The  O
exquisite  O
dish  O
cleverly  O
showcased  O
the  O
flavour  O
of  O
each  O
individual  O
ingredient  O
while  O
working  O
harmoniously  O
together  O
.  O
